<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-02-19T00:03:17.189Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-02-19T00:03:17.189Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Manage State in Your React Apps]]></title>
        <id>620fb6a621bfb3068cf2a92a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-manage-state-in-your-react-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T20:55:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managing state in your React apps isn’t as simple as using useState or useReducer. Not only are there are a lot of different kinds of state, but there often dozens of ways of managing each kind. Which should you choose? In this guide, we will uncover the several kinds of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove a Key from a Python Dictionary – Delete Key from Dict]]></title>
        <id>620ea69721bfb3068cf2a59b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-a-key-from-a-python-dictionary-delete-key-from-dict/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T20:32:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dictionary is a very powerful data collection in Python. Dictionaries help make database operations faster.  You can append items to an existing dictionary and remove them as well. In this blog post, we will learn how to delete "keys" using two methods:  1. Deleting key:value pairs using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Node JavaScript to JavaScript in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363467</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/node-javascript-compared-to-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T19:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to understand Node continues to be an important skill if you’re a front-end developer. Deno has arrived as another way to run JavaScript outside the browser, but the huge ecosystem of tools and software built with Node mean …
Comparing Node JavaScript to JavaScript in the Browser originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Install Python on Windows]]></title>
        <id>620f5f5e21bfb3068cf2a6d8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-install-python-in-windows-operating-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T16:14:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before trying to run any Python program in your Windows operating system, you'll need to check if you have Python installed and added to the environment's path variable correctly. In this article, I will show you how you can check whether you have Python installed successfully in your operating system]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VGA No Signal – How to Fix a Monitor Connection on Windows 10 PC]]></title>
        <id>620ecdf421bfb3068cf2a603</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vga-no-signal-how-to-fix-a-monitor-connection-on-windows-10-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T16:02:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes you might turn on your PC but your monitor displays "No Signal" on the screen. In this article, we will look at various solutions for solving this problem. How to Fix a Monitor Connection by Checking Hardware Connections  * Check to see if the VGA connector fits in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build a Custom Dashboard with WordPress APIs and React]]></title>
        <id>620d6f0321bfb3068cf29c08</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/build-a-custom-dashboard-with-wordpress-apis-and-react/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T15:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you manage websites, it is all about data: views, response time, users, bounce rate, and so on. And, if you manage websites, you've likely had to deal with a WordPress instance at least once.  There are hundreds – or maybe thousands – of WordPress plugins to retrieve and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marco Venturi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Jay Freestone’s) Front-End Predictions for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363911</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jay-freestone-front-end-predictions-for-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T15:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I linked to Jay’s front-end predictions last year and I think they panned out pretty well. I think he’s got a bit of a knack for that wide-scope look at front-end, including tooling and architecture, as well as browser tech. …
(Jay Freestone’s) Front-End Predictions for 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts On Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/thoughts-on-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/thoughts-on-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown in all its flavors, interpretations, and forks won’t go away. However, it’s important to look at emerging content formats that try to encompass modern needs. In this article, Knut shares his advice against Markdown by looking back on why it was introduced in the first place, and by going through some of the major developments of content on the web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Knut Melvær)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn C++ Programming for Beginners – Free 31-Hour Course]]></title>
        <id>620ed56e21bfb3068cf2a607</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-c-with-free-31-hour-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T23:16:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[C++ has been one of the most popular programming languages for over 30 years. Developers use it for everything from building video games to coding operating systems. We just published a comprehensive 31-hour C++ course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel. Daniel Gakwaya developed this course. Daniel is an experienced software]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Overflow – Visible, Scroll, Auto, or Hidden? The Overflow Property Explained]]></title>
        <id>6206b26756125b0677c646d3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/css-overflow-visible-scroll-auto-hidden/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T20:37:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial, we will talk about an important CSS property – the overflow  property.  It helps us control what happens when an element's content is too big to fit into an area. When this happens, it makes the content "overflow" into another area, either horizontally (X-axis) or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up VSCode for Your React Projects]]></title>
        <id>620e62a321bfb3068cf2a204</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/vscode-react-setup/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T16:54:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ultimate tool you have when you're developing your projects is your code editor. Which is why it's so important to set it up properly. In this step-by-step guide, we will go from a completely new VSCode installation to a code editor perfectly prepared for your next React project. Let's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reed Barger</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add Diagrams to GitHub Markdown Files]]></title>
        <id>620e67e821bfb3068cf2a29c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-add-diagrams-to-github-readme/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T16:37:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Previously, if you wanted to include a diagram in your GitHub README file, you would've needed to add it like an image created with third-party software.  This worked, and let us complete our tasks – but why settle for less when you can create a diagram within the README]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kaushal Joshi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Subsetting Font Awesome to Improve Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363179</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/subsetting-font-awesome-to-improve-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T15:21:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Font Awesome is an incredibly popular icon library. Unfortunately, it’s somewhat easy to use in a way that results in less-than-ideal performance. By subsetting Font Awesome, we can remove any unused glyphs from the font files it provides. This will …
Subsetting Font Awesome to Improve Performance originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Start a Freelance Dev Business]]></title>
        <id>61f7d395f2ed6b06db5a936a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-start-a-freelance-dev-business/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T15:04:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many people who want to try freelancing believe that they need to have years of experience to succeed. But this is a common misconception that many freelancers have disproved. Regardless of your industry, a helpful blueprint can be all you need to fast-track your freelancing success. This article underscores what]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Andrej Kovacevic</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Things You Didn’t Know You Could Do With Netlify CLI￼]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363872</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/top-things-you-didnt-know-you-could-do-with-netlify-cli/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
First things first, if you didn’t know Netlify had a CLI, they do.  One of my favorite things about it running the command netlify dev on nearly any static-site generator project is seeing it …
Top Things You Didn’t Know You Could Do With Netlify CLI￼ originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Add-to-Calendar Button UI Widget]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363861</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/add-to-calendar-button-ui-widget/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-17T01:14:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A useful little UI widget thingy here from Jens Kuerschner. Click the add-to-calendar button, get a list of calendar apps, the user selects which one they actually use, and they get what they need for that calendar. Could be a …
Add-to-Calendar Button UI Widget originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Auto-Filling CSS Grid With Max Columns of a Minimum Size]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363541</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/an-auto-filling-css-grid-with-max-columns/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T15:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Within Drupal 10 core, we’re implementing a new auto-filling CSS Grid technique that I think is cool enough to share with the world.
The requirements are:
The user specifies a maximum number of columns. This is the auto-filling grid’s “natural” 
…
An Auto-Filling CSS Grid With Max Columns of a Minimum Size originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Mike Herchel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling In Love With The Web: Inspiring Websites And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/inspiring-websites-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/inspiring-websites-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all need a little inspiration boost every now and again. In this post, we collected inspiring resources from all across the web for you — beautiful eye candy, tips to challenge your skills, and useful tools that are bound to spark new ideas. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSAP Flip Plugin for Animation]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363604</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/gsap-flip-plugin-for-animation/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T21:41:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Greensock made the GSAP Flip plugin free in the 3.9 release. FLIP is an animation concept that helps make super performance state-change animations. Ryan Mulligan has a good blog post: 
FLIP, coined by Paul Lewis, is an 
…
GSAP Flip Plugin for Animation originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Creative Ideas for CSS Link Hover Effects]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363124</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-link-hover-effects/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T15:37:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Creating CSS link hover effects can add a bit of flair to an otherwise bland webpage. If you’ve ever found yourself stumped trying to make a slick hover effect, then I have six CSS effects for you to take and …
6 Creative Ideas for CSS Link Hover Effects originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Harshil Patel</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress.com Has a New Home on YouTube]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363739</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/wordpress-com-has-a-new-home-on-youtube/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T15:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
✋ High fives to WordPress for releasing version 5.9 on January 29! This was the long-awaited introduction of the Site Editor and the reverberations are still being felt across the 43% slice of the …
WordPress.com Has a New Home on YouTube originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Geoff Graham</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implications Of WordPress Joining The Block Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/implications-wordpress-joining-block-protocol/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/implications-wordpress-joining-block-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz discusses some potential consequences as well as positive outcomes of WordPress joining the Block Protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why are hyperlinks blue?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363555</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/why-are-hyperlinks-blue/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T20:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last year, Elise Blanchard did some great historical research and discovered that blue hyperlinks replaced black hyperlinks in 1993. They’ve been blue for so long now that the general advice I always hear is to keep them that way. There …
Why are hyperlinks blue? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With the File System Access API]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363339</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/getting-started-with-the-file-system-access-api/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T16:01:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The File System Access API is a web API that allows read and write access to a user’s local files. It unlocks new capabilities to build powerful web applications, such as text editors or IDEs, image editing tools, improved …
Getting Started With the File System Access API originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Charlie Gerard</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Want To Know About Creating Voice User Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/voice-user-interfaces-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/voice-user-interfaces-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice is a powerful tool that we can use to communicate with each other. This article covers the most critical aspects of designing for voice user interfaces: designing the conversation and designing visual interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich &amp; Gleb Kuznetsov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.4]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.4</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.4"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T06:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Several style issues]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.3"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T06:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[style tweak]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.2"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T05:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New: Adjust article grouping based on timezone. You need to add timezone in osmosfeed.yml for accurate grouping. See details in documentation.
New: Card title now toggles card content
New: all toggles on the UI are persisted with local storage. You can use it to track read/unread status within a single browser.
New: Build timestamp now links to the GitHub Action run
Changed: Sources are sorted based on publish time rather than alphabetical order
Changed: Style adjusted for easier reading
Fixed: Horizontal overflow on Safari
Fixed: HTML syntax error in default template]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.1"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T05:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[git typo in gh run url]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.0: V1.14.0 (#79)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.0"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T05:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New: Adjust article grouping based on timezone. You need to add timezone in osmosfeed.yml for accurate grouping. See details in documentation.
New: Card title now toggles card content
New: all toggles on the UI are persisted with local storage. You can use it to track read/unread status within a single browser.
New: Build timestamp now links to the GitHub Action run
Changed: Sources are sorted based on publish time rather than alphabetical order
Changed: Style adjusted for easier reading
Fixed: Horizontal overflow on Safari
Fixed: HTML syntax error in default template]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.13.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.13.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.13.0"/>
        <updated>2022-02-13T05:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New: Thumbnail image display for each article
New: Improved color, spacing, and typography for easier reading
New: Click the date to toggle all accordions on that day. Ctrl + Click to toggle all accordions on the entire site.
Changed: All sections are expanded by default
Changed: Switched to vitest for easier testing
Fixed: Long string (e.g. URL) caused horizontal overflow
Thank you: @naari3, @tianheg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.12.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.12.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.12.1"/>
        <updated>2022-02-12T17:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Future articles appeared in the feed
Fxied: Security vulnerability from axios
Thank you: @naari3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Your CSS reset needs text-size-adjust (probably)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363498</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/your-css-reset-needs-text-size-adjust-probably/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-12T00:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kilian Valkhof:
[…] Mobile Safari increases the default font-size when you switch a website from portrait to landscape. On phones that is, it doesn’t do it on iPad. Safari has been doing this for a long time, as a 
…
Your CSS reset needs text-size-adjust (probably) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[9 New React and JavaScript Links for February 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363396</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/9-new-react-and-javascript-links-for-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T23:11:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every now and then, I find that I’ve accumulated a bunch of links about various things I find interesting. Like React and JavaScript! Here’s a list of nine links to other articles about them that I’ve been saving up and …
9 New React and JavaScript Links for February 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Value CSS Properties With Optional Custom Property Values]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363027</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/optional-custom-property-values-trick/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T15:30:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you have an element with a multi-value CSS property, such as transform: optional custom property values:
.el {
  transform: translate(100px) scale(1.5) skew(5deg);
}
Now imagine you don’t always want all the transform values to be applied, so some …
Multi-Value CSS Properties With Optional Custom Property Values originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Yair Even Or</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Perfectly Pointless]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-design-done-well-perfectly-pointless/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-design-done-well-perfectly-pointless/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This installment of *Web Design Done Well* celebrates weird and wacky websites. Sites with sweet, innocent, sometimes pointless purposes. Are they money makers? Game changers? Not necessarily, but they sure are fun, and in ways only the web could really manage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Whistle-Stop Tour of 4 New CSS Color Features]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=362285</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/new-css-color-features-preview/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-10T23:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I was just writing in my “What’s new in since CSS3?” article about recent and possible future changes to CSS colors. It’s weirdly a lot. There are just as many or more new and upcoming ways to define colors than …
A Whistle-Stop Tour of 4 New CSS Color Features originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fitts’ Law In The Touch Era]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/fitts-law-touch-era/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/fitts-law-touch-era/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Steven Hoober shines the spotlight on Fitts’ Law and explains why we should always ask questions and consider what particular guidelines and lessons mean to our users and our products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steven Hoober)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statoscope: A Course Of Intensive Therapy For Your Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/statoscope-course-intensive-therapy-bundle/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/statoscope-course-intensive-therapy-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Statoscope is an instrument that analyses your webpack-bundles. Created by Sergey Melukov, it started out as an experimental version in late 2016, which has now become a full-fledged toolkit for viewing, analyzing, and validating webpack-bundles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sergey Melukov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using QR Codes In Your Business: Best Practices And Pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/qr-codes-business-best-practices-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/qr-codes-business-best-practices-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While QR codes have many uses and can be leveraged at many touch points, they are just one of dozens of technologies that can improve the customer’s journey. Stanislav Khrustalev shares his advice with a list of things to keep in mind when using QR codes for your business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stanislav Khrustalev)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Web Frameworks Solve: The Vanilla Alternative (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-frameworks-guide-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-frameworks-guide-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-04T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second part, Noam suggests a few patterns of how to use the web platform directly as an alternative to some of the solutions that are offered by frameworks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Noam Rosenthal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Web’s Carbon Footprint: Optimizing Social Media Embeds]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/reducing-web-carbon-footprint-optimizing-social-media-embeds/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/reducing-web-carbon-footprint-optimizing-social-media-embeds/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll look specifically at what we can do to reduce the impact of social media embeds and social sharing widgets — or even some strategies to avoid them altogether. While the spotlight is on reducing the environmental impact, many of these tips will be great for performance too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving JavaScript Bundle Performance With Code-Splitting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/javascript-bundle-performance-code-splitting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/javascript-bundle-performance-code-splitting/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian Bece shares more about the benefits and caveats of code-splitting and how page performance and load times can be improved by dynamically loading expensive, non-critical JavaScript bundles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces”, A New Smashing Book]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/touch-design-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/touch-design-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s shipping! Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide with guidelines and best practices to improve usability and accessibility on mobile. 400 pages. For designers and developers working with mobile UIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[28 Days Of Inspiration (February 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for February 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Web Frameworks Solve And How To Do Without Them (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/web-frameworks-guide-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/web-frameworks-guide-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-28T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Noam Rosenthal dives deep into a few technical features that are common across frameworks, and explains how some of the different frameworks implement them and what they cost.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Noam Rosenthal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t Underestimate The Software Administration UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/software-administration-ux/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/software-administration-ux/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-26T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This article reveals how something as trivial as administration in both software and As-a-service can be either a booster or bottleneck to a company’s productivity and innovation. It also provides several design aspects that UX practitioners should evaluate when designing the administration experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Shell Zhu &amp; Adrian Jones)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What’s New In DevTools?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/devtools-updates-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/devtools-updates-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-25T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What’s new in Chrome, Edge, Safari and Firefox? Patrick Brosset breaks it down with the latest features in DevTools across browsers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Patrick Brosset)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With CSS Cascade Layers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/introduction-css-cascade-layers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/introduction-css-cascade-layers/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cascade layers introduce the new at-rule of @layer. The intent is to help CSS authors be more intentional about ordering the “layers” of CSS rules as a new method of cascade management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Chaos To System In Design Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/from-chaos-to-system-design-teams/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/from-chaos-to-system-design-teams/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joining a team where there are no established design practices may feel disheartening. Does this situation resonate with you? If yes, then read on — as this article is sharing the author’s advice based on his personal experience and it will show you a way (although not easy) of facing the problem in a manner that will bring other benefits, beside order and consistency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Javier Cuello)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building The Real App With React Query]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/building-real-app-react-query/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/building-real-app-react-query/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Georgii Perepecho explains the most common React Query features that you need to be familiar with when creating a real-life application that is stable when testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Georgii Perepecho)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>