<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-03-01T00:03:56.035Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-03-01T00:03:56.035Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364346</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ie-down-edge-up-global-browser-usage-stats-are-for-cocktail-parties-and-conference-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy articles like Hartley Charlton’s “Microsoft Edge Looks Set to Overtake Safari as World’s Second Most Popular Desktop Browser.” It’s juicy! We know these massive players in the browser market care very much about their market share, so when …
IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Best Python Courses to Take in 2022]]></title>
        <id>62160a08c4d0d306772eecd2</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-python-courses/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T19:56:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you want to learn Python, there are a lot of great resources out there. But if you're specifically looking for the best online course to learn Python, then you've come to the right place. In this article, I present a list of awesome Python courses ranked according to a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Elham Nazif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Uppercase – How to Capitalize a String in JS with .toUpperCase]]></title>
        <id>620c9b9621bfb3068cf2939d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-uppercase-how-to-capitalize-a-string-in-js-with-touppercase/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T19:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While working with strings in JavaScript, you can perform different operations on them. The operations you might perform on strings include capitalization, conversion to lowercase, adding symbols within words, and many more. In this article, I will show you how to convert a string to uppercase letters with the .toUpperCase()]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How I Went from Classical Musician to Software Developer using freeCodeCamp]]></title>
        <id>6213501a21bfb3068cf2bf5b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-i-went-from-a-classical-musician-to-software-developer-and-techinal-writer/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T19:11:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Before the pandemic, I spent my whole life performing, teaching, and composing music. But in June of 2020, I made the decision to learn how to code and successfully landed a job as a software developer. Here is the story of how I learned how to code using freeCodeCamp [https://www.freecodecamp.org/learn/]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Animation Performance Fundamentals – How to Make Your Pages Look Smooth]]></title>
        <id>61faafa3f2ed6b06db5ab1ab</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/web-animation-performance-fundamentals/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T18:49:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What if I told you that web pages were interactive animations played back by your web browser? We watch various motions every time we're on a web page.  And it's not only JavaScript or CSS animations that I'm talking about. Scrolling, pinch zooming, text selection, and even hovering over]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Reza Lavarian</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Multiline Comment – How to Comment Out Multiple Lines in Python]]></title>
        <id>620abfab21bfb3068cf288b5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-multiline-comment-how-to-comment-out-multiple-lines-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T17:54:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Commenting is an integral part of every programming language. With comments, you get a better understanding of your own code, make it more readable, and can help team members understand how it works. Comments are ignored by compilers and interpreters, so they don’t run. Apart from making your code more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get the ASCII Value of Any Character with One Line of Code]]></title>
        <id>6213533d21bfb3068cf2bf8c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/get-the-ascii-value-of-any-character-with-one-line-of-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T16:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working on a project or computer program, you might need to use the ASCII value of a certain character.  This is a common phenomenon in competitive programming, as well – we typically need to use the ASCII value of characters when solving some of the problems on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363929</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-component-pseudo-classes-and-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T15:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve discussed a lot about the internals of using CSS in this ongoing series on web components, but there are a few special pseudo-elements and pseudo-classes that, like good friends, willingly smell your possibly halitotic breath before you go …
Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Best Webstorm Plugins for Effective Coding]]></title>
        <id>62013885f2ed6b06db5af06e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/best-webstorm-plugins-for-effective-coding/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T15:01:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a software developer, I use a variety of plugins that make my life easier when it comes to avoiding mistakes and coding more efficiently. Whilst these time and effort saving techniques may seem negligible as a one off, when accumulated together they can really make a difference. In this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ania Kubow</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 5 Best Code Editors for Mac – MacOS Text Editor Guide]]></title>
        <id>617db19e33422e07df36811e</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/the-5-best-code-editors-for-mac-macos-text-editor-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T14:46:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding, you're writing various text that can be executed by different language compilers. And what makes this text fun and easy to write are the editors that we use. Different editors have different features. But they have a common goal: making writing code easier – easier to compose,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We All Are Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a design community, we all can’t be silent in these times. We need to be united in our fight against the war, for democracy, for those dreams that children are entitled to have when they are growing up. It’s our obligation to help as much as we can. **We are donating all proceeds** from "Interface Design Checklists" PDF to support Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March For Equality (2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following our monthly tradition, artists and designers from across the globe challenged their creative skills and designed desktop wallpapers to welcome March. They come in versions with and without a calendar and can be downloaded for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Recipe For A Good Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining a design system is a lot of work. In this article, Atila Fassina shares his lessons learned and how a platform such as Backlight can help put together a series of tools to speed up your architecture setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Section Divider Using CSS]]></title>
        <id>6217ea59c4d0d306772ef522</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/section-divider-using-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T21:46:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's always cool to have a fancy section divider on your website. And it's even better if we can make them responsive and easy to adjust. This is what you will learn in this article. We will explore different section dividers made using only CSS and some optimized code that's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trailing Slashes on URLs: Contentious or Settled?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/trailing-slashes-on-urls-contentious-or-settled/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T21:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fun deep dive from Zach. Do you have an opinion on which you should use?
1) https://website.com/foo/
2) https://websites.com/foo
The first option has a “trailing slash.” The second does not.
I’ve always preferred this thinking: you use a trailing …
Trailing Slashes on URLs: Contentious or Settled? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Avoid the text-decoration Shorthand Property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363619</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-to-avoid-css-text-decoration-shorthand/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T15:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my recent article about CSS underline bugs in Chrome, I discussed text-decoration-thickness and text-underline-offset, two relatively new and widely-supported CSS properties that give us more control over the styling of underlines.
Let me demonstrate the usefulness of …
When to Avoid the text-decoration Shorthand Property originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzovic’s CSS Specificity Demo]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364152</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/manuel-matuzovics-css-specificity-demo/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a primer on CSS specificity, we’ve got that. And if you’re trying to get ahead of the game, you should be aware of CSS Cascade Layers as well.
One of the ways to help get …
Manuel Matuzovic’s CSS Specificity Demo originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My white whale: A use case for will-change]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/my-white-whale-a-use-case-for-will-change/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T20:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nic Chan:
[…] the will-change property landed in major browsers in August 2015, and I’ve been on the lookout for when to use it ever since. It might seem self-evident to apply it to commonly animated properties such 
…
My white whale: A use case for will-change originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Find in List – How to Find the Index of an Item or Element in a List]]></title>
        <id>6213c94921bfb3068cf2c268</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-find-in-list-how-to-find-the-index-of-an-item-or-element-in-a-list/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T20:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you will learn how to find the index of an element contained in a list in the Python programming language. There are a few ways to achieve this, and in this article you will learn three of the different techniques used to find the index of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Explain the First 10 Lines of Twitter’s Source Code to Me]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363553</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/explain-the-first-10-lines-of-twitter-source-code/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T15:31:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For the past few weeks, I’ve been hiring for a senior full-stack JavaScript engineer at my rental furniture company, Pabio. Since we’re a remote team, we conduct our interviews on Zoom, and I’ve observed that some developers are not …
Explain the First 10 Lines of Twitter’s Source Code to Me originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Anand Chowdhary</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superior Image Optimization: An Ideal Solution Using Gatsby & ImageEngine]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363526</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/superior-image-optimization-an-ideal-solution-using-gatsby-imageengine/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T15:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
In recent years, the Jamstack methodology for building websites has become increasingly popular. Performance, scalable, and secure, it’s easy to see why it’s becoming an attractive way to build websites for developers.
GatsbyJS is …
Superior Image Optimization: An Ideal Solution Using Gatsby & ImageEngine originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>ImageEngine</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Benchmark And Improve Web Vitals With Real User Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/benchmark-improve-web-vitals-real-user-metrics/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/benchmark-improve-web-vitals-real-user-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Vitals are the new gold standard in performance due to their direct correlation with the user’s experience. In this article, you’ll learn what monitoring can do and how RayGun can help you sustain performance maintenance while scaling your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Database Queries? Sure We Can!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363937</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-database-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T20:04:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kinda silly sounding, isn’t it? CSS database queries. But, hey, CSS is capable of talking to other languages in the sense that it can set the values of things that they can read. Plus, CSS can request other files, and …
CSS Database Queries? Sure We Can! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Accessibility Quick Wins You Can Implement Today]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363532</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/5-accessibility-quick-wins-you-can-implement-today/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T15:15:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s face it: building an AA or AAA-accessible product can be quite daunting. Luckily, having an accessible product isn’t all-or-nothing. Even seemingly small improvements can have nice quality of life benefits for many people.
In that spirit, here are five …
5 Accessibility Quick Wins You Can Implement Today originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Yuschick</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using The WordPress Editor And CPTs To Configure Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/wordpress-editor-cpts-configure-plugins/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/wordpress-editor-cpts-configure-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we want our WordPress plugins to offer a settings page that is fully powered by blocks, how can we do it? Since *Full Site Editing* doesn’t support this feature yet, we need to code a custom solution. In this article, we will learn how we can do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Before I go: When it comes to complaining about web browsers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363998</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/before-i-go-when-it-comes-to-complaining-about-web-browsers/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T20:06:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[That’s a damn one-two punch from Dave. He goes for the ultimate clickbait title¹, then follows up with a pile of epic advice for us all. If you want web browsers to get better, listen up:
Complaining on 
…
Before I go: When it comes to complaining about web browsers originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reliably Send an HTTP Request as a User Leaves a Page]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363511</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/send-an-http-request-on-page-exit/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T15:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On several occasions, I’ve needed to send off an HTTP request with some data to log when a user does something like navigate to a different page or submit a form. Consider this contrived example of sending some information to …
Reliably Send an HTTP Request as a User Leaves a Page originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alex MacArthur</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Develop A Text Editor For The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/develop-text-editor-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/develop-text-editor-web/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do text typing and editing work on the web? Although this process might seem straightforward, there is a lot of technical nuance behind its apparent simplicity. This article looks at how typing on the web works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Medvedev)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 45 With Jeremy Wagner: What Is Responsible JavaScript?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/smashing-podcast-episode-45/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/smashing-podcast-episode-45/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we’re talking about Responsible JavaScript. What does it mean for code to be responsible, and how should we approach projects differently? Drew McLellan talks to expert Jeremy Wagner to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide to CSS Cascade Layers]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363766</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-cascade-layers/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T15:40:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This is your complete guide to CSS cascade layers, a CSS feature that allows us to define explicit contained layers of specificity, so that we have full control over which styles take priority in a project without relying on specificity …
A Complete Guide to CSS Cascade Layers originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Miriam Suzanne</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing Pipeline 101 For Frontend Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/testing-pipeline-101-frontend-testing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/testing-pipeline-101-frontend-testing/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-21T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You don’t need to be a full DevOps engineer if you want to introduce a testing build routine. With the help of some testing frameworks and GitHub actions, Ramona Schwering gives a short kick-off to help you get on the right track.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ramona Schwering)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Comparing Node JavaScript to JavaScript in the Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363467</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/node-javascript-compared-to-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T19:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being able to understand Node continues to be an important skill if you’re a front-end developer. Deno has arrived as another way to run JavaScript outside the browser, but the huge ecosystem of tools and software built with Node mean …
Comparing Node JavaScript to JavaScript in the Browser originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Hugh Haworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Jay Freestone’s) Front-End Predictions for 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363911</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/jay-freestone-front-end-predictions-for-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T15:34:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I linked to Jay’s front-end predictions last year and I think they panned out pretty well. I think he’s got a bit of a knack for that wide-scope look at front-end, including tooling and architecture, as well as browser tech. …
(Jay Freestone’s) Front-End Predictions for 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thoughts On Markdown]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/thoughts-on-markdown/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/thoughts-on-markdown/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Markdown in all its flavors, interpretations, and forks won’t go away. However, it’s important to look at emerging content formats that try to encompass modern needs. In this article, Knut shares his advice against Markdown by looking back on why it was introduced in the first place, and by going through some of the major developments of content on the web.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Knut Melvær)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Falling In Love With The Web: Inspiring Websites And Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/inspiring-websites-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/inspiring-websites-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-16T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all need a little inspiration boost every now and again. In this post, we collected inspiring resources from all across the web for you — beautiful eye candy, tips to challenge your skills, and useful tools that are bound to spark new ideas. Enjoy!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implications Of WordPress Joining The Block Protocol]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/implications-wordpress-joining-block-protocol/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/implications-wordpress-joining-block-protocol/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-15T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Leonardo Losoviz discusses some potential consequences as well as positive outcomes of WordPress joining the Block Protocol.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everything You Want To Know About Creating Voice User Interfaces]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/voice-user-interfaces-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/voice-user-interfaces-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Voice is a powerful tool that we can use to communicate with each other. This article covers the most critical aspects of designing for voice user interfaces: designing the conversation and designing visual interfaces.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich &amp; Gleb Kuznetsov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.4]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.4</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.4"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T06:58:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Several style issues]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.3]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.3</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.3"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T06:29:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[style tweak]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.2]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.2</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.2"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T05:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New: Adjust article grouping based on timezone. You need to add timezone in osmosfeed.yml for accurate grouping. See details in documentation.
New: Card title now toggles card content
New: all toggles on the UI are persisted with local storage. You can use it to track read/unread status within a single browser.
New: Build timestamp now links to the GitHub Action run
Changed: Sources are sorted based on publish time rather than alphabetical order
Changed: Style adjusted for easier reading
Fixed: Horizontal overflow on Safari
Fixed: HTML syntax error in default template]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.1"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T05:26:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[git typo in gh run url]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.14.0: V1.14.0 (#79)]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.14.0"/>
        <updated>2022-02-14T05:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New: Adjust article grouping based on timezone. You need to add timezone in osmosfeed.yml for accurate grouping. See details in documentation.
New: Card title now toggles card content
New: all toggles on the UI are persisted with local storage. You can use it to track read/unread status within a single browser.
New: Build timestamp now links to the GitHub Action run
Changed: Sources are sorted based on publish time rather than alphabetical order
Changed: Style adjusted for easier reading
Fixed: Horizontal overflow on Safari
Fixed: HTML syntax error in default template]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.13.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.13.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.13.0"/>
        <updated>2022-02-13T05:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New: Thumbnail image display for each article
New: Improved color, spacing, and typography for easier reading
New: Click the date to toggle all accordions on that day. Ctrl + Click to toggle all accordions on the entire site.
Changed: All sections are expanded by default
Changed: Switched to vitest for easier testing
Fixed: Long string (e.g. URL) caused horizontal overflow
Thank you: @naari3, @tianheg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.12.1]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.12.1</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.12.1"/>
        <updated>2022-02-12T17:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fixed: Future articles appeared in the feed
Fxied: Security vulnerability from axios
Thank you: @naari3]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Design Done Well: Perfectly Pointless]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-design-done-well-perfectly-pointless/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-design-done-well-perfectly-pointless/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This installment of *Web Design Done Well* celebrates weird and wacky websites. Sites with sweet, innocent, sometimes pointless purposes. Are they money makers? Game changers? Not necessarily, but they sure are fun, and in ways only the web could really manage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Frederick O’Brien)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fitts’ Law In The Touch Era]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/fitts-law-touch-era/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/fitts-law-touch-era/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-09T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Steven Hoober shines the spotlight on Fitts’ Law and explains why we should always ask questions and consider what particular guidelines and lessons mean to our users and our products.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steven Hoober)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Statoscope: A Course Of Intensive Therapy For Your Bundle]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/statoscope-course-intensive-therapy-bundle/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/statoscope-course-intensive-therapy-bundle/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-08T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Statoscope is an instrument that analyses your webpack-bundles. Created by Sergey Melukov, it started out as an experimental version in late 2016, which has now become a full-fledged toolkit for viewing, analyzing, and validating webpack-bundles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sergey Melukov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using QR Codes In Your Business: Best Practices And Pitfalls]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/qr-codes-business-best-practices-pitfalls/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/qr-codes-business-best-practices-pitfalls/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-07T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While QR codes have many uses and can be leveraged at many touch points, they are just one of dozens of technologies that can improve the customer’s journey. Stanislav Khrustalev shares his advice with a list of things to keep in mind when using QR codes for your business.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stanislav Khrustalev)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Web Frameworks Solve: The Vanilla Alternative (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-frameworks-guide-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/web-frameworks-guide-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-04T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this second part, Noam suggests a few patterns of how to use the web platform directly as an alternative to some of the solutions that are offered by frameworks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Noam Rosenthal)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reducing The Web’s Carbon Footprint: Optimizing Social Media Embeds]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/reducing-web-carbon-footprint-optimizing-social-media-embeds/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/reducing-web-carbon-footprint-optimizing-social-media-embeds/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-03T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll look specifically at what we can do to reduce the impact of social media embeds and social sharing widgets — or even some strategies to avoid them altogether. While the spotlight is on reducing the environmental impact, many of these tips will be great for performance too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving JavaScript Bundle Performance With Code-Splitting]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/javascript-bundle-performance-code-splitting/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/javascript-bundle-performance-code-splitting/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Adrian Bece shares more about the benefits and caveats of code-splitting and how page performance and load times can be improved by dynamically loading expensive, non-critical JavaScript bundles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meet “Touch Design For Mobile Interfaces”, A New Smashing Book]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/touch-design-release/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/touch-design-release/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s shipping! Meet “Touch Design for Mobile Interfaces”, our brand-new guide with guidelines and best practices to improve usability and accessibility on mobile. 400 pages. For designers and developers working with mobile UIs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[28 Days Of Inspiration (February 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Do you need a little inspiration boost? Well, then our new batch of desktop wallpapers is for you. Designed by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for February 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>