<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-03-24T00:03:40.329Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-03-24T00:03:40.329Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Create a List in Python – Lists in Python Syntax]]></title>
        <id>623af0d3cdcd57069ddfd5bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-a-list-in-python-lists-in-python-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T20:32:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Lists are one of the core data structures in Python. We use them for storing any data type, whether it's an integer, string, boolean, or even an object. Because one list can store multiple types of data, lists are one of the most powerful and widely used tools for storing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes Security – Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures for K8s Programs]]></title>
        <id>6230d789c3e3d106805db72a</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/kubernetes-security-common-vulnerabilities-and-exposures/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T19:06:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Kubernetes has become the go-to tool for orchestration, scaling, automated deployment, and management of containerized applications.  Simply put, Kubernetes is a system that maintains coordination between diverse applications across a group of machines. It is important to note that this system mostly deals with containerized applications, like Docker images.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Prajwal Kulkarni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use *args and **kwargs in Python]]></title>
        <id>623a9306cdcd57069ddfd494</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/args-and-kwargs-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T18:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll discuss *args and **kwargs in Python along with their uses and some examples. When writing a function, we often need to pass values to the function. These values are called function arguments.  Problem with Function Arguments Let's define a function to add two numbers in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ashutosh Krishna</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Add a MetaMask Login to Your Laravel Web Application]]></title>
        <id>6238bd3dcdcd57069ddfc5ad</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/add-a-metamask-login-to-your-laravel-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T18:38:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Logging into a website via third parties is ubiquitous online. Almost every other member-based website allows you to log in with accounts like Facebook, Twitter, and Google. If you’ve ever visited NFT marketplaces like OpenSea or Rarible, you would have noticed they allow you to sign in with a crypto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Darren Chowles</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those HTML Attributes You Never Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Louis Lazaris describes and demonstrates some interesting HTML attributes that you may or may not have heard of and perhaps find useful enough to personally use in one of your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Taxes for Freelance Developers – How Much Tax You Should Pay as a Freelancer]]></title>
        <id>6238d5a4cdcd57069ddfc7db</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/taxes-for-freelance-developers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T13:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Disclaimer: This article should not be construed as advice for tax management or investment decisions.  Neither the author of this article, nor freeCodeCamp, are professionals in these areas. The discussion below is a matter of personal opinion only and you should discuss such matters with a licensed professional. If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Luke Ciciliano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Is WordPress a Code or No-code Tool?]]></title>
        <id>6236e318cdcd57069ddfbc09</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/is-wordpress-a-code-or-no-code-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T01:56:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress is an open-source content management system (CMS) for building any kind of website – an eCommerce site, a portfolio, a forum, and many more. WordPress started out as a simple platform for creating blogs, but today WordPress powers over 43% of the total websites on earth, and that number]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Else-If in Python – Python If Statement Example Syntax]]></title>
        <id>623848d7cdcd57069ddfc40d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/else-if-in-python-python-if-statement-example-syntax/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T20:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're coding, you need to be able to check certain conditions and change the control of the program execution accordingly.  Python provides many conditional statements for decision making, and if-else is one of them. In this blog post, we will learn:  1. The default order of execution]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Go Programming by Building 11 Projects]]></title>
        <id>623a17b2cdcd57069ddfd0b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-go-by-building-11-projects/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T18:50:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Go programming language is an open-source and compiled language designed by Google. Go is popular for cloud-based or server-side applications. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will help you improve your Go skills by teaching you how to create eleven projects. Akhil Sharma developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Remove the Start Text from PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>62358f0ccdcd57069ddfb8b4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-remove-starting-text-from-powershell/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T17:18:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are using a Windows operating system, you have likely used the latest Windows PowerShell at least once.  Whenever you open the PowerShell, you get a text message inside the terminal which shows the terminal version, the link to download the latest PowerShell, and so on.  Sometimes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Design Is All About Good Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this shorter series of articles, we highlight design patterns, techniques, and strategies to design better digital interfaces. You can also learn much more in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python Operator – Logical Operators in Python]]></title>
        <id>62346eeacdcd57069ddfae72</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/operators-in-python-how-to-use-logical-operators-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T00:21:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operators in any programming language are the basic building blocks using which we can construct powerful, complex statements for problem solving.  Python offers different types of operators, like arithmetic operators, logical operators, relational operators and so on. In this post, let's dive into logical operators in Python and learn]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Suchandra Datta</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/write-html-the-html-way-not-the-xhtml-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not use XHTML (anymore), but when you write HTML, you may be more influenced by XHTML than you think. You are very likely writing HTML, the XHTML way.
What is the XHTML way of writing HTML, and what …
Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Oliver Meiert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows High Contrast Mode, Forced Colors Mode And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Properties can be used for far more than just color, and their values update in realtime, both via display mode updates and JavaScript logic. This is powerful stuff. Eric explains how modern CSS is a powerful piece of assistive technology that can thread into it to create flexible, maintainable and adaptive digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364090</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/optimizing-svg-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently created a brick wall pattern as part of my #PetitePatterns series, a challenge where I create organic-looking patterns or textures in SVG within 560 bytes (or approximately the size of two tweets). To fit this constraint, I have …
Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bence Szabó</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make A Drag-and-Drop File Uploader With Vue.js 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building on a previous article on How to Build a Drag-and-Drop File Uploader, we’ll be adding some new features, but more importantly (maybe), we’ll be learning how to build it in Vue 3 and learn some best practices for Vue along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joseph Zimmerman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claymorphism: Will It Stick Around?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fresh new design trend has been picking up steam with the rising popularity of colorful inflated 3D graphics in web illustrations and with the latest Virtual Reality projects like “Horizon Worlds”. Let’s see if there is room for Claymorphism on the UI, and how we can create this effect with CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365042</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-is-joining-digitalocean/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T12:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey!
I’ve got a big announcement to make here. (Where’s my gong? I feel like this really needs a good gong hit.)
CSS-Tricks, this very website you’re looking at, has been acquired by DigitalOcean!
You can hear …
CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The CI/CD Flow For Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for ways to create a smooth CI/CD flow for your software? In this article, Tom Hastjarjanto shares some useful concepts that can be combined with GitHub Actions and NPM packages. With this setup, you will be able to release multiple times per hour with a fully documented trace managed by Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hastjarjanto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Mobile App Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standing out among the millions of mobile apps can be challenging, but proper marketing can give you that crucial edge. This piece shares how to start your mobile app marketing strategy and improve it as you go while keeping up with the latest trends in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sona Dabaghyan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Vivek Maskara introduces Amazon Web Services’ (AWS) Cloud Development Kit (CDK) which is increasingly becoming a popular tool for managing AWS-based infrastructure. We’ll take a closer look into CDK concepts, and then how to use the AWS CDK toolkit to deploy a sample application to an AWS account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vivek Maskara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Audio Visualization With JavaScript And GSAP (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What started as a case study turned into a guide to visualizing audio with JavaScript. Although the output demos are in React, Jhey Tompkins isn’t going to dwell on the React side of things too much. The underlying techniques work with or without React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Signals For Customizing Website UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using signals to deliver less, or different, content is a form of progressive enhancement (or graceful degradation depending on how you look at it), whereby extraneous content is only loaded when necessary, but the core functionality of the website still works. In this article, we’ll look at some of the signals that can be used for this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create An Information Architecture That Is Easy To Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/easy-information-architecture/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/easy-information-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If users cannot find the answers to their questions or are not exposed to critical messaging, they will not act, and your website will fail. To prevent that from happening, you need an effective information architecture. In this article, Paul Boag provides you with a process to ensure you have precisely that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say Hello to selectmenu, a Fully Style-able select Element]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363972</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-selectmenu-element/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T15:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to introduce you to a new, experimental form control called <selectmenu>. We’ll get deep into it, including how much easier it is to style than a traditional <select> element. But first, let’s fill in some context …
Say Hello to selectmenu, a Fully Style-able select Element originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Brosset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Membership Businesses with Memberful]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364001</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/build-membership-businesses-with-memberful/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T15:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
What would your business be like if you sold memberships? It might be more than fun to think about, in fact, it might just be transformative. With membership, would you include little add-ons or …
Build Membership Businesses with Memberful originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Web Layouts For Dual-Screen And Foldable Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/building-web-layouts-dual-screen-foldable-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/building-web-layouts-dual-screen-foldable-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dual-screen devices are just the next evolution in responsive design. If you have a PWA or website, the APIs available make integrating into your existing code base seamless. This article explains why it’s an exciting time for layout on the web, and how dual screens provide an opportunity to get even more creative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Stimac)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Fresh Links on Performance For March 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364350</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/performance-links-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T21:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a handful of good links to articles about performance that are burning a hole in my bookmarks folder, and wanna drop them here to share.
The new WebPageTest website design
From fonts to SVG: an icon migration strategy
…
7 Fresh Links on Performance For March 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a “Raise the Curtains” Effect in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363882</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-raise-the-curtains-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T15:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Raise the curtains” is what I call an effect where the background goes from dark to light on scroll, and the content on top also goes from light to dark while in a sticky position.
Here’s an example where I …
How to Make a “Raise the Curtains” Effect in CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvestar Bistrović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Audio Visualization With JavaScript And GSAP (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What started as a case study turned into a guide to visualizing audio with JavaScript. Although the output demos are in React, Jhey Tompkins isn’t going to dwell on the React side of things too much. The underlying techniques work with or without React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Highlight API: The Future of Highlighting Text Ranges on the Web]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-custom-highlight-api-early-loo/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T17:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Styling ranges of text in software is a very useful thing to be able to do. Thankfully, we have the CSS Custom Highlight API to look forward to because it represents the future of styling text ranges on the web.…
CSS Custom Highlight API: The Future of Highlighting Text Ranges on the Web originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Brosset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed: Use Cases For CSS fit-content]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364351</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ahmad-shadeed-use-cases-for-css-fit-content/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T15:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed covers the CSS fit-content sizing keyword. It’s useful! It just doesn’t come up super often. I find myself using min-content a lot more, like when setting up the height of a grid-template-row.
The fit-content keyword is actually …
Ahmad Shadeed: Use Cases For CSS fit-content originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Features In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/new-css-features-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/new-css-features-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 is shaping up to be a pretty great year for CSS, with a plethora of new features on the horizon. Some are already starting to land in browsers, others are likely to gain widespread browser support in 2022, while for one or two the process may be a little longer. In this article we’ll take a look at a few of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364346</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ie-down-edge-up-global-browser-usage-stats-are-for-cocktail-parties-and-conference-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy articles like Hartley Charlton’s “Microsoft Edge Looks Set to Overtake Safari as World’s Second Most Popular Desktop Browser.” It’s juicy! We know these massive players in the browser market care very much about their market share, so when …
IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We All Are Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a design community, we all can’t be silent in these times. We need to be united in our fight against the war, for democracy, for those dreams that children are entitled to have when they are growing up. It’s our obligation to help as much as we can. **We are donating all proceeds** from "Interface Design Checklists" PDF to support Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363929</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-component-pseudo-classes-and-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T15:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve discussed a lot about the internals of using CSS in this ongoing series on web components, but there are a few special pseudo-elements and pseudo-classes that, like good friends, willingly smell your possibly halitotic breath before you go …
Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March For Equality (2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following our monthly tradition, artists and designers from across the globe challenged their creative skills and designed desktop wallpapers to welcome March. They come in versions with and without a calendar and can be downloaded for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Recipe For A Good Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining a design system is a lot of work. In this article, Atila Fassina shares his lessons learned and how a platform such as Backlight can help put together a series of tools to speed up your architecture setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trailing Slashes on URLs: Contentious or Settled?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364070</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/trailing-slashes-on-urls-contentious-or-settled/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T21:13:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A fun deep dive from Zach. Do you have an opinion on which you should use?
1) https://website.com/foo/
2) https://websites.com/foo
The first option has a “trailing slash.” The second does not.
I’ve always preferred this thinking: you use a trailing …
Trailing Slashes on URLs: Contentious or Settled? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When to Avoid the text-decoration Shorthand Property]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363619</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/when-to-avoid-css-text-decoration-shorthand/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T15:28:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my recent article about CSS underline bugs in Chrome, I discussed text-decoration-thickness and text-underline-offset, two relatively new and widely-supported CSS properties that give us more control over the styling of underlines.
Let me demonstrate the usefulness of …
When to Avoid the text-decoration Shorthand Property originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Šime Vidas</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Manuel Matuzovic’s CSS Specificity Demo]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364152</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/manuel-matuzovics-css-specificity-demo/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-25T15:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re looking for a primer on CSS specificity, we’ve got that. And if you’re trying to get ahead of the game, you should be aware of CSS Cascade Layers as well.
One of the ways to help get …
Manuel Matuzovic’s CSS Specificity Demo originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[My white whale: A use case for will-change]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364138</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/my-white-whale-a-use-case-for-will-change/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T20:59:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nic Chan:
[…] the will-change property landed in major browsers in August 2015, and I’ve been on the lookout for when to use it ever since. It might seem self-evident to apply it to commonly animated properties such 
…
My white whale: A use case for will-change originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Benchmark And Improve Web Vitals With Real User Metrics]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/benchmark-improve-web-vitals-real-user-metrics/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/benchmark-improve-web-vitals-real-user-metrics/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-24T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Vitals are the new gold standard in performance due to their direct correlation with the user’s experience. In this article, you’ll learn what monitoring can do and how RayGun can help you sustain performance maintenance while scaling your app.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using The WordPress Editor And CPTs To Configure Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/wordpress-editor-cpts-configure-plugins/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/wordpress-editor-cpts-configure-plugins/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-23T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If we want our WordPress plugins to offer a settings page that is fully powered by blocks, how can we do it? Since *Full Site Editing* doesn’t support this feature yet, we need to code a custom solution. In this article, we will learn how we can do it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Leonardo Losoviz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Develop A Text Editor For The Web]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/develop-text-editor-web/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/develop-text-editor-web/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-22T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How do text typing and editing work on the web? Although this process might seem straightforward, there is a lot of technical nuance behind its apparent simplicity. This article looks at how typing on the web works.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ilya Medvedev)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>