<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-01-25T00:03:22.275Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-01-25T00:03:22.275Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.12.0</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Temporal Dead Zone (TDZ) and Hoisting in JavaScript – Explained with Examples]]></title>
        <id>61e92726183181284a191e75</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-temporal-dead-zone-and-hoisting-explained/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T23:10:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Temporal Dead Zone and Hoisting are two essential terms in JavaScript. But understanding how they work can easily confuse you if you don't approach them properly. But don't fret! This article is here to help you get a good grasp of the two terms. So relax, grab your favorite cup]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python String.Replace() – Function in Python for Substring Substitution]]></title>
        <id>61ebdebf011f8933034705af</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-string-replace-function-in-python-for-substring-substitution/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T16:59:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you'll see how to use Python's .replace() method to perform substring substiution.  You'll also see how to perform case-insensitive substring substitution.  Let's get started!  What does the .replace() Python method do? When using the .replace() Python method, you are able to replace every instance of one specific]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn Programming – Free Software Development Courses for Beginners]]></title>
        <id>61d543e4d2d9de084285c33d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-programming-free-software-development-courses-for-beginners/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T16:05:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, I'm going to show you 140 beginner friendly courses where you can learn computer science and programming for free. The freeCodeCamp courses are completely free and some of them include a free certification that you can add to your LinkedIn or résumé. Note that some of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Don’t Developers Take Accessibility Seriously?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360811</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/why-dont-developers-take-accessibility-seriously/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T14:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You know that joke, “Two front-end developers walk into a bar and find they have nothing in common”? It’s funny, yet frustrating, because it’s true.
This article will present three different perspectives on accessibility in web design and development. Three …
Why Don’t Developers Take Accessibility Seriously? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Melanie Sumner</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Getting Started With CSS Cascade Layers]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/introduction-css-cascade-layers/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/introduction-css-cascade-layers/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cascade layers introduce the new at-rule of @layer. The intent is to help CSS authors be more intentional about ordering the “layers” of CSS rules as a new method of cascade management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Eckles)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using SVG in WordPress (2 Helpful Plugin Recommendations)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360346</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/using-svg-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T19:35:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SVG is a great image format, so it's nice to able to use it in WordPress. If you're looking to be using SVG in WordPress. , we've got you covered here with all the best options.
Using SVG in WordPress (2 Helpful Plugin Recommendations) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make Event Sourcing in Java Easier]]></title>
        <id>61e3bb40b837d507ba0a3f30</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-make-event-sourcing-in-java-easier/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T16:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event sourcing is about persisting events instead of just the current state. Event sourcing can be helpful for auditing purposes, and to analyze or rebuild previous system states for business analysis. Let's look at it in a bit more detail: every time you make a change to the application state,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Administrator Has Blocked You From Running This App –  How to Fix on a Windows 10 PC]]></title>
        <id>61ea53d4fa0e660c3ce47514</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/an-administrator-has-blocked-you-from-running-this-app-how-to-fix-on-a-windows-10-pc/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T15:51:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes when you decide to open an app or file or install or open a program on your Windows 10 PC, you might get the error "An administrator has blocked you from running this app".  You get this error because Windows 10 is optimized for protection against malware]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Chaos To System In Design Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/from-chaos-to-system-design-teams/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/from-chaos-to-system-design-teams/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Joining a team where there are no established design practices may feel disheartening. Does this situation resonate with you? If yes, then read on — as this article is sharing the author’s advice based on his personal experience and it will show you a way (although not easy) of facing the problem in a manner that will bring other benefits, beside order and consistency.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Javier Cuello)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Context-Aware Web Components Are Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360665</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/context-aware-web-components/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-21T14:08:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Another aspect of web components that we haven’t talked about yet is that a JavaScript function is called whenever a web component is added or removed from a page. These lifecycle callbacks can be used for many things, including making …
Context-Aware Web Components Are Easier Than You Think originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Delete a Disk or Storage Device in Windows Using the GUI and the CLI]]></title>
        <id>61e95a08183181284a1922e8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-format-storage-disk-in-windows-gui-cli/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T20:20:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deleting or formatting a disk or storage device is a common task for most computer users.  If you use the Windows operating system, you would normally do that using the GUI Disk Management application which comes built-in with any Windows operating system. Disk Management (GUI)Sometimes, you might have difficulties]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Destructuring in JavaScript – How to Destructure Arrays and Objects]]></title>
        <id>61e940e8183181284a19209d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/destructuring-patterns-javascript-arrays-and-objects/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T18:27:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Working with JavaScript arrays and objects can be more fun if you destructure them. This helps when you're fetching stored data. In this article, you will learn how you can take destructuring to the next level in JavaScript arrays and objects. Table of contents:What is an array?What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[List Index Out of Range – Python Error Message Solved]]></title>
        <id>61e30fbfb837d507ba0a3b8f</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/list-index-out-of-range-python-error-message-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T16:03:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article you'll see a few of the reasons that cause the list index out of range Python error.  Besides knowing why this error occurs in the first place, you'll also learn some ways to avoid it.  Let's get started!  How to Create a List in Python To create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Define Cloud Infrastructure with the AWS Cloud Development Kit]]></title>
        <id>61e981bd183181284a1925ba</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/aws-cloud-development-kit-crash-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Instead of setting up your cloud infrastructure manually, it can be easier and safer to use code. The AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK) is an open-source software development framework to define your cloud application resources using familiar programming languages. We just published a crash course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Beginner’s Guide to npm]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361210</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-complete-beginners-guide-to-npm/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:07:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
I remember vividly a period early in my coding career when I began to feel that things were changing away from what I knew, and headed towards a more complex set of tools and …
A Complete Beginner’s Guide to npm originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Heck Does “npm” Mean?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361214</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-clear-definition-of-npm-and-what-it-does/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the things that makes this new, tooling-heavy era of front-end development so seemingly hard to understand at first is that, while we often call things by a singular name, they tend to be actually comprised of several different …
What the Heck Does “npm” Mean? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Heck is the Command Line?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361226</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-deep-look-at-the-command-line/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:04:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now that we know what npm stands for and have a super general idea of what it does and how it fits into web development, we ought to spend a little bit of time looking at the command line, because …
What the Heck is the Command Line? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Heck is Node?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361241</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/node-and-how-it-works-with-npm/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:04:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
Here’s what you need to know about Node.js (or simply Node) and how it relates to npm right off the bat:
Node is JavaScript, but as a server-side language.
This is possible because of 
…
What the Heck is Node? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Heck is a Package Manager?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361257</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-the-heck-is-a-package-manager/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re keeping score, so far in this npm guide we’ve developed a general understanding of what npm is—notably, that it stands for Node Package Manager. In the process, we’ve discussed the importance of the command line and how it’s …
What the Heck is a Package Manager? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Heck Do You Install npm?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361270</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-install-npm-node-nvm/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:03:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Feel like you have a pretty good idea of what a package manager is? We’ve certainly covered a lot of ground getting familiar with all the terms and concepts of package managers, but I’d say it’s high time we actually …
How the Heck Do You Install npm? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Heck Do You Install npm Packages?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361300</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-install-npm-packages/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:03:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, you’re becoming quite knowledgeable with npm! So far, we’ve broken down the three letters in “npm” to gain a better understand of Node and package managers. In the previous chapter, we even installed Node and npm while …
How the Heck Do You Install npm Packages? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What the Heck Are npm Commands?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361320</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/what-the-heck-are-npm-commands/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:03:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[npm is, as you now know, a package manager. But like similar, earlier tools that run tasks in the command line, such as Grunt and Gulp, npm can also run tasks—which is perfect for us because now that …
What the Heck Are npm Commands? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How the Heck Do You Install an Existing npm Project?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=361337</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-install-an-npm-project/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T15:03:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
We’ve gotten a good overview of how npm works and how to use it to install packages and run commands at this point. Now let’s go a little further and see what it looks …
How the Heck Do You Install an Existing npm Project? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Josh Collinsworth</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building The Real App With React Query]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/building-real-app-react-query/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/building-real-app-react-query/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-20T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Georgii Perepecho explains the most common React Query features that you need to be familiar with when creating a real-life application that is stable when testing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Georgii Perepecho)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Serene CSS Dappled Light Effect]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360899</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-dappled-light-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T22:46:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a serene warmth to the early evening sunlight peaking through rustling leaves. Artists use dappled light to create a soft, hypnotic effect.
Bedford Dwellings by Ron Donoughe (2013)
We can create the same sort of dappled light effect in …
A Serene CSS Dappled Light Effect originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[freeCodeCamp Just Got a Million Dollar Donation from an Alum to Build a Carbon-Neutral Web3 Curriculum]]></title>
        <id>61e79b46183181284a191680</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/carbon-neutral-web3-curriculum-plans/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T21:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A freeCodeCamp alum who founded his own successful Web3 company has donated $1M to freeCodeCampHe asked that we use some of these funds to develop a carbon-neutral Web3 curriculumWe are building an interactive Web3 curriculum where you can learn by building more than a dozen projects. This free curriculum will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>freeCodeCamp.org</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What should someone learn about CSS if they last boned up during CSS3?]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=359857</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/whats-new-since-css3/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T14:25:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What's new in CSS? If someone asked you that, who knows CSS but hasn't stayed up to date the last, say, half a decade or more, what advice would you give?
What should someone learn about CSS if they last boned up during CSS3? originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upcoming Online Workshops: January &ndash; May 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/smashingconf-workshops-january-may-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/smashingconf-workshops-january-may-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What goes into creating a successful design system? How can you take your testing workflow to the next level? And what smart interface design patterns could help you enhance your UIs? Let’s figure it out. With our [online workshops on front-end and UX](https://smashingconf.com/online-workshops).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Quality Options for a Table of Contents Block in WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=360362</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/table-of-contents-block-in-wordpress/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T23:22:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There are a number of options for including a Table of Contents lock in WordPress. You can use a plugin, or try to do it yourself. 
4 Quality Options for a Table of Contents Block in WordPress originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter and become a supporter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Freebie: Wayfinding Icon Sets (164 Icons, PNG, SVG, AI, EPS)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/freebie-wayfinding-icon-sets-exhibition-concert-museum/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/freebie-wayfinding-icon-sets-exhibition-concert-museum/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-18T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every once in a while, we publish [freebies](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/category/freebies) related to different occasions and themes. We hope that with this icon set, everyone will be able to find their own use case for these icons in particular. Today, we present to you three icon sets designed by the creative folks at GraphicSurf — all free for personal and commercial use.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Anton Tyschenko)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modern Fluid Typography Using CSS Clamp]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/modern-fluid-typography-css-clamp/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/modern-fluid-typography-css-clamp/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-17T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ll explore fluid typography principles, use-cases, implementation with CSS clamp() and an interactive fluid typography calculator.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Tips For Aspiring Designer Beginners (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/ten-tips-aspiring-designer-beginners-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/ten-tips-aspiring-designer-beginners-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-14T15:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In [Part 1](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/ten-tips-aspiring-designer-beginners-part1/), Luis Ouriach shared advice he wished he had when starting out in his career. In this second and last part of this series, Luis continues sharing tips that helped him grow and become a better designer throughout the years.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building A Web Code Editor]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/building-web-code-editor/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/building-web-code-editor/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-13T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’re a developer who’s thinking about building a platform that requires a code editor in one form or another, then this article is for you. This article explains how to create a web code editor that displays the result in real time with the help of some HTML, CSS and JavaScript.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Daniel Don)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Hire For Digital Accessibility Roles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/how-hire-digital-accessibility-roles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/how-hire-digital-accessibility-roles/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Accessibility must be a permanent program within organizations, much like security. In this article, Kate Kalcevich shares tips on which skills and questions to keep in mind when hiring for digital accessibility roles.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Kate Kalcevich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Deep CSS Dive Into Radial And Conic Gradients]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/css-radial-conic-gradient/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/css-radial-conic-gradient/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll be taking a closer look at two gradients: `conic-gradient` and `radial-gradient`. You’ll see how each one of them works in detail, what the differences and similarities are between them, how and where to use them, and some use cases for each.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ahmad Shadeed)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[v1.12.0]]></title>
        <id>https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.12.0</id>
        <link href="https://github.com/osmoscraft/osmosfeed/releases/tag/v1.12.0"/>
        <updated>2022-01-10T05:25:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New: When one of the sources download fails, fall back to cache and continue rest of the build.
Chore: Dependency updates
Added docs for Netlify deployment
Fixed #71 #69 #65
Thank you: @sokomin, @molakirlee, @philippnagel, @tianheg]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Release notes from osmosfeed</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Changing A Tire On A Moving Car (Or How To Improve Product Roadmaps)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/changing-tire-on-moving-car/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/changing-tire-on-moving-car/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-07T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Product roadmaps are often treated as a series of checkboxes. But they are more than that. In this article, Scott Himmer explains how internal partnerships, research, design systems, and regular touch bases can help make sure that your product roadmap is a successful one.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Scott Himmer)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ten Tips For Aspiring Designer Beginners (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/ten-tips-aspiring-designer-beginners-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/ten-tips-aspiring-designer-beginners-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article (the first part in a series of two), Luis Ouriach shares advice that he wishes he has when starting out in his career. These tips come from his experience as a user interface and product designer for close to ten years, and if you’re starting just now, then read on!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Luis Ouriach)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Composition-Based Design System In Figma]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/composition-based-design-system-figma/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/01/composition-based-design-system-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-01-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Figma has advanced enough where it now supports some powerful concepts that can help with the flexibility and maintainability of a design system. In this article, Sasha explains why she finds the Systems Designer position so rewarding — and it’s not only because of how fast certain tools have developed to help her master challenges she faces in her work projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Aleksandra Nagornaia)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Year, Fresh Desktop (January 2022 Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-january-2022/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-31T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What better way could there be to start the new year than with some fresh inspiration? Our collection of wallpapers for January 2022 is bound to put a smile on your face — and maybe spark new ideas, too.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Price Projects And Manage Scope Creep]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/how-price-projects-manage-scope-screep/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/how-price-projects-manage-scope-screep/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scoping, estimating, and running digital projects can often feel like an exercise in futility. In this article, Paul Boag explains why you need to start breaking your projects down into manageable phases and why that’s the best way to achieve significant benefits.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Gatsby Themes For WordPress-Powered Websites]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/building-gatsby-themes-wordpress-powered-websites/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2021/12/building-gatsby-themes-wordpress-powered-websites/"/>
        <updated>2021-12-27T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you already built and published a Gatsby theme? In this article, Paulina Hetman explains how Gatsby themes work and what problems they can solve by comparing Gatsby themes with their WordPress counterparts.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paulina Hetman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>