<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-04-12T00:03:56.782Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-12T00:03:56.782Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set Up a Virtual Environment in Python – And Why It's Useful]]></title>
        <id>6250c642ac55f60686c3023c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-setup-virtual-environments-in-python/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:46:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When developing software with Python, a basic approach is to install Python on your machine, install all your required libraries via the terminal, write all your code in a single .py file or notebook, and run your Python program in the terminal. This is a common approach for a lot]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Stephen Sanwo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Sandbox Tutorial – How to Enable Sandbox On Windows]]></title>
        <id>62515952ac55f60686c304b7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-enable-sandbox-on-windows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T20:13:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Sandbox is a temporary lightweight desktop environment that you can use to safely run Windows applications in an isolated space.  The software or applications that you install inside the Windows sandbox environment remain "sandboxed", and they all run separately from the host machine. So whatever happens in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Learn the C++ Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>624447b2138a19064b0683f8</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-learn-the-c-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T17:10:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the early days of computer programming, programmers had to write individual instructions in the Assembly language one by one.  Later on programming languages like FORTRAN and COBOL were created. The problem with these languages was that they were targeted at a certain group of people – FORTRAN for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Farhan Hasin Chowdhury</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DNS Server Not Responding – Service Unavailable DNS Failure [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>624e9e37ac55f60686c2f16b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/dns-server-not-responding-service-unavailable-dns-failure-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:59:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes, you might suddenly discover that you can’t access the internet on your computer because of the error “DNS server not responding”. If you run a troubleshooter for the issue, you'll get a message like the below: In your Chrome browser, you might also get an error like the one]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create and Upload Your First Python Package to PyPI]]></title>
        <id>624da2d3ac55f60686c2eb3c</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-and-upload-your-first-python-package-to-pypi/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:40:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A few weeks ago, I wanted to learn how to build my first Python package, and I was trying to figure out where to start.  Well, I got confused and a bit stressed trying to find a simple and easy tutorial I could use to get started. For this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Rochdi Khalid</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use the Git Stash Command]]></title>
        <id>62459f78138a19064b069268</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/git-stash-commands/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T15:05:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's say you're working on a serious feature of a branch in Git – like revamping the hero section of your marketing page. You'll want to start doing experiments in your Revamp/Marketing-page-hero-section branch without screwing up master or main branch. Then suddenly you get call from your coworker to fix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi⚡</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boost Resource Loading With fetchpriority, a New Priority Hint]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boost-resource-loading-new-priority-hint-fetchpriority/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boost-resource-loading-new-priority-hint-fetchpriority/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-11T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This new attribute will enable us to fine-tune relative resource priority, improve LCP performance, deprioritize JavaScript fetch calls, and much more. Let’s check out fetchpriority and explore some potential use cases.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python If-Else Statement Example]]></title>
        <id>62530365ac55f60686c316e5</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/python-if-else-statement-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T17:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If-Else statements – AKA conditional logic – are the bedrock of programming. And Python has these in spades. Python offers several options for evaluating variables, their states, and whether specific conditions are met:  * Vanilla if-else statements  * if statements without the else part  * nested if-else]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PMP Certification Cost – 2022 Exam Fees, Degree Requirements, and Years of Experience]]></title>
        <id>6252eea7ac55f60686c315af</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/pmp-certification-cost-degree-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-10T15:44:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Project Management Professional (PMP) is widely seen by project managers as the "gold standard" credential. Many senior PM roles now require you to be PMP certified. So if you have been working as a PM for a few years, this guide will show you how you can take the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Image File Types – The .jpeg, .svg, and .png Picture Format Extensions Explained]]></title>
        <id>62518273ac55f60686c30623</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/image-file-types-picture-format-extensions-jpeg-gif-png-svg-tiff/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-09T22:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you’re working with images, it’s important to understand the different file types. Which format is best for what application? In this tutorial, we’re going to explain the most common image file types, and when you should use them. Note that this is a short, non-technical article. If you want]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Quincy Larson</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic Data-Fetching In An Authenticated Next.js App]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/dynamic-data-fetching-authenticated-nextjs-app/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/dynamic-data-fetching-authenticated-nextjs-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is among the most important things that make up a web application or a conventional native app. We need data to be able to see and perhaps understand the purpose of an application. In this article, we’ll look at another approach to obtaining data in an application that requires authentication or authorization using Next.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Caleb Olojo)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Force Delete a File – Windows Command Prompt cmd delete]]></title>
        <id>624c24d2ac55f60686c2e356</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-force-delete-a-file-windows-command-prompt-cmd-delete/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-08T07:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On a Windows computer, you might want to delete files to free up disk space, or because you don't want the file(s) on your computer anymore. But sometimes, it seems impossible to delete a file for various reasons. These include the file being open in another program, lack of write]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Breadcrumbs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-breadcrumbs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of articles, we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can also find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Devs For Ukraine, A Free Online Charity Conference 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/devs-for-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[[Devs For Ukraine](https://www.devsforukraine.io/) is a free online charity conference organized by the lovely people at Remote. Two days filled with talks from engineering leaders around the globe, in support of Ukraine. April 25–26.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get Work Done: Wrangling Stakeholders And Overcoming Obstacles]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/stakeholders-overcoming-obstacles/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-05T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Whether you work in-house or for an external agency, we all share one challenge — dealing with stakeholders, be they your boss, colleagues, or clients. In this post, veteran web designer Paul Boag shares his approach to getting things done in even the most challenging organizations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364166</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-cdn-caching-to-a-vite-build/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T18:25:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Content delivery networks, or CDNs, allow you to improve the delivery of your website’s static resources, most notably, with CDN caching. They do this by serving your content from edge locations, which are located all over the world. When a …
Adding CDN Caching to a Vite Build originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Build A Progressively Enhanced, Accessible, Filterable And Paginated List]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/accessible-filterable-paginated-list-11ty-alpinejs/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever wondered how to build a paginated list that works with and without JavaScript? In this article, Manuel explains how you can leverage the power of Progressive Enhancement and do just that with Eleventy and Alpine.js.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Manuel Matuzović)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The What, When, Why And How Of Next.js’ New Middleware Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js’ recent 12.0 release included a new beta feature: middleware. For a detailed explanation, you can read all about it in Sam’s previous article, “[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/)”. This article, on the other hand, dives into the overall concept of middleware and how handy it can be in building things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time For Reflection (April 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some new wallpapers. Designed with love by artists and designers from across the globe, they are available in versions with and without a calendar for April 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364279</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cut-corners-using-css-mask-and-clip-path-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently covered creating fancy borders with CSS mask properties, and now we are going to cut the corners with CSS mask and clip-path! A lot of techniques exist to cut different shapes from the corners of any element. …
Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Infinite Scroll]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Best practices and guidelines to improve the UX of infinite scroll with bookmarks, footer reveal and pagination.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SmashingConf Is Back In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years when almost everything moved online, 2022 marks the return of in-person conferences. In fact, [SmashingConf is back](https://smashingconf.com/conferences): coming to  San Francisco and Austin in June, Freiburg (Germany) in September, and New York in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jarijn Nijkamp)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobs For Designers And Developers Affected By The War In Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a designer or developer affected by the war in Ukraine? Here are some options to consider if you’re looking for a design or tech job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-development-bookmarklets/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T18:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bookmarklet is a JavaScript-based bookmark that adds to a web browser. I’d like to show you some awesome web browser hacks to aid your web development workflow and how to convert those hacks into time-saving bookmarklets.
Activating design mode
…
6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Hover And Pointer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll talk about how to adapt our sites to the different scenarios of a device pointer: whether it has a pointer or not, or how accurate it is. To adapt our site to those devices’ needs we’ll talk about how to properly use media queries `hover`, `pointer`, `any-hover` and `any-pointer`.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remix Routes Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past months, there have been lots of talks dedictaed to Remix. Routing is not only one of the things that sets it apart from other frameworks, but it also fuels great performance and improves the overall experience for developers. Let’s dig in to all  of the features that build up routing in this powerful framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those HTML Attributes You Never Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Louis Lazaris describes and demonstrates some interesting HTML attributes that you may or may not have heard of and perhaps find useful enough to personally use in one of your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Design Is All About Good Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this shorter series of articles, we highlight design patterns, techniques, and strategies to design better digital interfaces. You can also learn much more in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/write-html-the-html-way-not-the-xhtml-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not use XHTML (anymore), but when you write HTML, you may be more influenced by XHTML than you think. You are very likely writing HTML, the XHTML way.
What is the XHTML way of writing HTML, and what …
Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Oliver Meiert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows High Contrast Mode, Forced Colors Mode And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Properties can be used for far more than just color, and their values update in realtime, both via display mode updates and JavaScript logic. This is powerful stuff. Eric explains how modern CSS is a powerful piece of assistive technology that can thread into it to create flexible, maintainable and adaptive digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364090</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/optimizing-svg-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently created a brick wall pattern as part of my #PetitePatterns series, a challenge where I create organic-looking patterns or textures in SVG within 560 bytes (or approximately the size of two tweets). To fit this constraint, I have …
Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bence Szabó</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make A Drag-and-Drop File Uploader With Vue.js 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building on a previous article on How to Build a Drag-and-Drop File Uploader, we’ll be adding some new features, but more importantly (maybe), we’ll be learning how to build it in Vue 3 and learn some best practices for Vue along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joseph Zimmerman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claymorphism: Will It Stick Around?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fresh new design trend has been picking up steam with the rising popularity of colorful inflated 3D graphics in web illustrations and with the latest Virtual Reality projects like “Horizon Worlds”. Let’s see if there is room for Claymorphism on the UI, and how we can create this effect with CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365042</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-is-joining-digitalocean/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T12:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey!
I’ve got a big announcement to make here. (Where’s my gong? I feel like this really needs a good gong hit.)
CSS-Tricks, this very website you’re looking at, has been acquired by DigitalOcean!
You can hear …
CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The CI/CD Flow For Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for ways to create a smooth CI/CD flow for your software? In this article, Tom Hastjarjanto shares some useful concepts that can be combined with GitHub Actions and NPM packages. With this setup, you will be able to release multiple times per hour with a fully documented trace managed by Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hastjarjanto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>