<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-04-03T00:04:00.660Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-04-03T00:04:00.660Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Pass Callback Functions to String.replace() in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>6246e84d138a19064b06a1c9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-pass-callback-functions-to-string-replace-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T20:14:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that the string .replace() method accepts a callback function? I just discovered it today and thought I'd share. What do you need this function for? Why does it exist? I'll answer all these questions as you go through this article. The replace() Method The replace() string method]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create a Rate Limiter using Bucket4J and Redis]]></title>
        <id>6245914c138a19064b0690bb</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/rate-limiting-with-bucket4j-and-redis/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T19:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this tutorial we will learn how to implement rate limiting in a scaled service. We will use the Bucket4J [https://github.com/vladimir-bukhtoyarov/bucket4j]  library to implement it and we will use Redis [https://redis.io/] as a distributed cache. Why Use Rate Limiting? Let's get started with some basics to make sure we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Abhinav Pandey</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a Full Stack Developer? 2022 Full Stack Engineer Guide]]></title>
        <id>6228642863ded806bb9e6f73</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-full-stack-developer-full-stack-engineer-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:42:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Full-stack developer roles are among the most highly sought after positions in the current job market. But what exactly is full-stack web development, and how do you become a full-stack developer? In this article, you will first learn what the term full-stack means. Then, you will see some suggested technologies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dionysia Lemonaki</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SQL Inner Join – How to Join 3 Tables in SQL and MySQL]]></title>
        <id>6164065d804854468fda843b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/sql-inner-join-how-to-join-3-tables-in-sql-and-mysql/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T18:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you're working with your database, you might need to put together data from a few different tables. This article will show you how. I have already written about SQL joins here [/news/sql-join-types-inner-join-vs-outer-join-example/] and here [/news/sql-left-join-example-join-statement-syntax/], but let's take a moment to review how a join works first, and particularly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ilenia Magoni</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NextJS and HarperDB Tutorial –Build a Full Stack Productivity Timer App]]></title>
        <id>6244a14e138a19064b0686c7</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/nextjs-and-harperdb-tutorial-build-a-full-stack-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T16:25:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building full stack applications can be tough. You have to think about frontend, APIs, databases, authentication - and how all of these things work together. So, in this article, I'll show you how to do all of those things using NextJS and HarperDB. We'll be building a full stack task]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Danny Adams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The What, When, Why And How Of Next.js’ New Middleware Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/next-js-middleware-feature/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Next.js’ recent 12.0 release included a new beta feature: middleware. For a detailed explanation, you can read all about it in Sam’s previous article, “[Next.js Wildcard Subdomains](https://www.smashingmagazine.com/2021/11/nextjs-wildcard-subdomains/)”. This article, on the other hand, dives into the overall concept of middleware and how handy it can be in building things.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sam Poder)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Apps with Firebase]]></title>
        <id>6245d985138a19064b069946</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/create-apps-with-firebase/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-01T00:10:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Firebase is a platform developed by Google for creating mobile and web applications.  We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to use Firebase. This is the perfect course for beginners.  After learning the basics of Firebase, you will learn how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shell Scripting for Beginners – How to Write Bash Scripts in Linux]]></title>
        <id>623cc7e0138a19064b06474d</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shell-scripting-crash-course-how-to-write-bash-scripts-in-linux/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T19:26:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shell scripting is an important part of process automation in Linux. Scripting helps you write a sequence of commands in a file and then execute them.  This saves you time because you don't have to write certain commands again and again. You can perform daily tasks efficiently and even]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shopify Email Automation – How to Automatically Send Emails]]></title>
        <id>62421c54138a19064b0672c6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/shopify-email-automation/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T17:00:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Email automation is not something new in the e-commerce space. And it's a pretty simple and straightforward concept. Email automation is all about sending emails to customers based on events that occur on your website, like abandoned cart emails, order confirmation emails, shipping confirmation emails, and so on. The result?]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Edan Ben-Atar</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented Reality Full Course]]></title>
        <id>6245d736138a19064b0698d9</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/augmented-reality-full-course/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:40:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Augmented reality is a technology that lets people superimpose digital content, such as images, sounds & text, over a real-world environment. We just published a 12-hour course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you about augmented reality from a theoretical and practical perspective. Priyanshu Bhattaharjee developed this course.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[charAt() in Java – How to Use the Java charAt() Method]]></title>
        <id>62445137138a19064b068407</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/charat-in-java-how-to-use-the-java-charat-method-2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T16:10:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The charAt() method in Java returns the char value of a character in a string at a given or specified index. In this article, we'll see how to use the charAt() method starting with it's syntax and then through a few examples/use cases.  How to Use the Java charAt()]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Time For Reflection (April 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-april-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-31T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome the new month with some new wallpapers. Designed with love by artists and designers from across the globe, they are available in versions with and without a calendar for April 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364279</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cut-corners-using-css-mask-and-clip-path-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T16:35:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We recently covered creating fancy borders with CSS mask properties, and now we are going to cut the corners with CSS mask and clip-path! A lot of techniques exist to cut different shapes from the corners of any element. …
Tricks to Cut Corners Using CSS Mask and Clip-Path Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Infinite Scroll]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/designing-better-infinite-scroll/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-30T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this series of articles, we highlight design patterns and techniques to design better interfaces. You can also find more examples in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SmashingConf Is Back In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/smashingconf-workshops-conferences-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After two years when almost everything moved online, 2022 marks the return of in-person conferences. In fact, [SmashingConf is back](https://smashingconf.com/conferences): coming to  San Francisco and Austin in June, Freiburg (Germany) in September, and New York in October.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jarijn Nijkamp)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jobs For Designers And Developers Affected By The War In Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/jobs-designers-developers-war-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-29T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are you a designer or developer affected by the war in Ukraine? Here are some options to consider if you’re looking for a design or tech job.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364118</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-development-bookmarklets/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T18:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A bookmarklet is a JavaScript-based bookmark that adds to a web browser. I’d like to show you some awesome web browser hacks to aid your web development workflow and how to convert those hacks into time-saving bookmarklets.
Activating design mode
…
6 Useful Bookmarklets to Boost Web Development originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Daniel Schwarz</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Hover And Pointer Media Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-hover-pointer-media-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-28T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we’ll talk about how to adapt our sites to the different scenarios of a device pointer: whether it has a pointer or not, or how accurate it is. To adapt our site to those devices’ needs we’ll talk about how to properly use media queries `hover`, `pointer`, `any-hover` and `any-pointer`.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cristian Díaz)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remix Routes Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past months, there have been lots of talks dedictaed to Remix. Routing is not only one of the things that sets it apart from other frameworks, but it also fuels great performance and improves the overall experience for developers. Let’s dig in to all  of the features that build up routing in this powerful framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those HTML Attributes You Never Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Louis Lazaris describes and demonstrates some interesting HTML attributes that you may or may not have heard of and perhaps find useful enough to personally use in one of your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Design Is All About Good Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this shorter series of articles, we highlight design patterns, techniques, and strategies to design better digital interfaces. You can also learn much more in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/write-html-the-html-way-not-the-xhtml-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not use XHTML (anymore), but when you write HTML, you may be more influenced by XHTML than you think. You are very likely writing HTML, the XHTML way.
What is the XHTML way of writing HTML, and what …
Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Oliver Meiert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows High Contrast Mode, Forced Colors Mode And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Properties can be used for far more than just color, and their values update in realtime, both via display mode updates and JavaScript logic. This is powerful stuff. Eric explains how modern CSS is a powerful piece of assistive technology that can thread into it to create flexible, maintainable and adaptive digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364090</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/optimizing-svg-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently created a brick wall pattern as part of my #PetitePatterns series, a challenge where I create organic-looking patterns or textures in SVG within 560 bytes (or approximately the size of two tweets). To fit this constraint, I have …
Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bence Szabó</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make A Drag-and-Drop File Uploader With Vue.js 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building on a previous article on How to Build a Drag-and-Drop File Uploader, we’ll be adding some new features, but more importantly (maybe), we’ll be learning how to build it in Vue 3 and learn some best practices for Vue along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joseph Zimmerman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claymorphism: Will It Stick Around?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fresh new design trend has been picking up steam with the rising popularity of colorful inflated 3D graphics in web illustrations and with the latest Virtual Reality projects like “Horizon Worlds”. Let’s see if there is room for Claymorphism on the UI, and how we can create this effect with CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365042</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-is-joining-digitalocean/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T12:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey!
I’ve got a big announcement to make here. (Where’s my gong? I feel like this really needs a good gong hit.)
CSS-Tricks, this very website you’re looking at, has been acquired by DigitalOcean!
You can hear …
CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The CI/CD Flow For Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for ways to create a smooth CI/CD flow for your software? In this article, Tom Hastjarjanto shares some useful concepts that can be combined with GitHub Actions and NPM packages. With this setup, you will be able to release multiple times per hour with a fully documented trace managed by Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hastjarjanto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Mobile App Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standing out among the millions of mobile apps can be challenging, but proper marketing can give you that crucial edge. This piece shares how to start your mobile app marketing strategy and improve it as you go while keeping up with the latest trends in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sona Dabaghyan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Vivek Maskara introduces Amazon Web Services’ (AWS) Cloud Development Kit (CDK) which is increasingly becoming a popular tool for managing AWS-based infrastructure. We’ll take a closer look into CDK concepts, and then how to use the AWS CDK toolkit to deploy a sample application to an AWS account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vivek Maskara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Audio Visualization With JavaScript And GSAP (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What started as a case study turned into a guide to visualizing audio with JavaScript. Although the output demos are in React, Jhey Tompkins isn’t going to dwell on the React side of things too much. The underlying techniques work with or without React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Signals For Customizing Website UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using signals to deliver less, or different, content is a form of progressive enhancement (or graceful degradation depending on how you look at it), whereby extraneous content is only loaded when necessary, but the core functionality of the website still works. In this article, we’ll look at some of the signals that can be used for this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>