<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-05-18T00:04:05.296Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-05-18T00:04:05.296Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Improve SQL Server Performance]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-sql-server-performance/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-improve-sql-server-performance/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T17:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SQL server performance can be tricky. But there are a lot of things you can do to increase the speed of your queries. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to improve performance on SQL Server. Rajan Arora developed this course. Rajan]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Axios React – How to Make Get, Post, and Delete API Requests]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/axios-react-how-to-make-get-post-and-delete-api-requests/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/axios-react-how-to-make-get-post-and-delete-api-requests/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T16:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Axios [https://axios-http.com/] is an HTTP client library based on promises. It makes sending asynchronous HTTP requests to REST endpoints easier and helps you perform CRUD operations. This REST endpoint/API could be an external API like the Google API, GitHub API, and so on – or it could be your own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Joel Olawanle</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Break in Python – Nested For Loop Break if Condition Met Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-in-python-nested-for-loop-break-if-condition-met-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/break-in-python-nested-for-loop-break-if-condition-met-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T15:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Loops in programming let us execute a set of instructions/block of code continuously until a certain condition is met.  We can also use loops to iterate over a collection of data and perform a similar operation on each item in the data set. names = ["John", "Jane", "Doe"] for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving Icons for UI Elements with Typographic Alignment and Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365531</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/improving-icons-for-ui-elements-with-typographic-alignment-and-scale/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T14:30:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Utilizing icons in user interface elements is helpful. In addition to element labeling, icons can help reinforce a user element’s intention to users. But I have to say, I notice a bit of icon misalignment while browsing the web. Even …
Improving Icons for UI Elements with Typographic Alignment and Scale originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Marcel Moreau</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Modern Way To Create And Host A WordPress Site]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/elementor-modern-way-create-host-wordpress-site/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/elementor-modern-way-create-host-wordpress-site/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s take a closer look at how you can create your very own WordPress site up and running created and hosted with the Elementor Cloud Website.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nick Babich)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smashing Podcast Episode 46 With Vitaly Friedman: Who Is Elliot Jay Stocks?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/smashing-podcast-episode-46/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/smashing-podcast-episode-46/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-17T04:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode, we ask how one man can go from designing websites for local bands to heading up Google Fonts Knowledge. Smashing’s Vitaly Friedman talks to Elliot Jay Stocks to find out.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Drew McLellan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Promises – The promise.then, promise.catch and promise.finally Methods Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promise-methods/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/javascript-promise-methods/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:30:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A promise is an object in JavaScript that will produce a value sometime in the future. This usually applies to asynchronous operations. In applications, asynchronous operations happen a lot. This can be API requests, delayed data processing, and much more. Instead of having to block code execution until the data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[JavaScript Arrays - How to Create an Array in JavaScript]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-array-in-javascript/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-an-array-in-javascript/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T18:17:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An array is a type of data structure where you can store an ordered list of elements.  In this article, I will show you 3 ways you can create an array using JavaScript.  I will also show you how to create an array from a string using the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Entry-Level Tech Jobs – Beginner IT Jobs with No Experience Required]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/entry-level-tech-job-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/entry-level-tech-job-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:51:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entry-level jobs hire people with little or no experience in that job. There are plenty of entry-level tech jobs on the market these days because of the ever-growing demand for technology-savvy workers.  There are many reasons to join the tech industry such as competitive salaries, promising career paths, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Zaira Hira</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Excel Absolute Reference – Cell Referencing Example]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-absolute-reference-cell-referencing-example/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/excel-absolute-reference-cell-referencing-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:29:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In Excel, you can use both absolute and relative cell referencing to make calculations. Relative referencing is the default. So, for example, whenever you extend a formula down some cells, the cells change based on the relationships of the rows and columns. What if you want each cell to lock]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Structures in JavaScript – With Code Examples]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-structures-in-javascript-with-examples/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/data-structures-in-javascript-with-examples/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T17:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi everyone! In this article we're going to take a look at a key topic when it comes to computer science and software development: data structures. It's definitely a must know topic for anyone working in the software development world, but it can be hard to understand and even a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Germán Cocca</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Become a Quality Assurance Engineer – QA Engineer Career Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-quality-assurance-engineer-qa-engineer-career-guide/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-become-a-quality-assurance-engineer-qa-engineer-career-guide/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Quality Assurance (QA) Engineer is someone who tests software products throughout the whole development process. They ensure that the product meets high quality standards before releasing it to the public. But how do you become a QA Engineer? In this article, I will talk about the qualifications and process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jessica Wilkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Backup Your Hashnode Articles to GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-backup-hashnode-articles-to-github/</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-backup-hashnode-articles-to-github/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T15:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many developers have a personal blog on Hashnode [https://hashnode.com/], one of the most popular blogging communities for people exploring tech.  I also write on Hashnode, but recently I was thinking about whether there is any way to backup my published articles to GitHub. Fortunately, I have found an easy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md. Fahim Bin Amin</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Style Variations in WordPress Block Themes]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365377</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-style-variations-in-wordpress-block-themes/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T14:38:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Global styles, a feature of the block themes, is one of my favorite parts of creating block themes. The concept of global style variations in WordPress were introduced in Gutenberg 12.5 which would allow theme authors to create alternate …
Creating Style Variations in WordPress Block Themes originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ganesh Dahal</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rethinking Server-Timing As A Critical Monitoring Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/rethinking-server-timing-monitoring-tool/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/rethinking-server-timing-monitoring-tool/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What makes the underused `Server-Timing` header uniquely powerful among all other response headers? We’ll rethink the expectation for using it exclusively for timing and see fast solutions for hard-to-solve monitoring challenges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sean Roberts)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool Hover Effects That Use CSS Text Shadow]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365738</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cool-hover-effects-that-use-css-text-shadow/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T14:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last article we saw how CSS background properties allow us to create cool hover effects. This time, we will focus on the CSS text-shadow property to explore even more interesting hovers. You are probably wondering how adding shadow …
Cool Hover Effects That Use CSS Text Shadow originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Tasks: To Focus On What Matters You Must De-Focus On What Doesn’t]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/top-tasks-focus-what-matters-must-defocus-what-doesnt/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/top-tasks-focus-what-matters-must-defocus-what-doesnt/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-13T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We waste so much today. One way of focusing on what truly matters is by identifying Top Tasks for yourself. Learn how to make tough decisions by focusing on the real, quantifiable evidence that will help create a better experience for your users.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Gerry McGovern)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A CSS Slinky in 3D? Challenge Accepted!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365706</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/a-css-slinky-in-3d/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T14:27:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Braydon Coyer recently launched a monthly CSS art challenge. He actually had reached out to me about donating a copy of my book Move Things with CSS to use as a prize for the winner of the challenge — …
A CSS Slinky in 3D? Challenge Accepted! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Use Google CrUX To Analyze And Compare The Performance Of JS Frameworks]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/google-crux-analysis-comparison-performance-javascript-frameworks/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/google-crux-analysis-comparison-performance-javascript-frameworks/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-12T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Dan Shappir analyzes the performance cost associated with various frameworks and explains the wide variety of framework and platform choices that are currently available to front-end and fullstack developers.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Dan Shappir)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[COLRv1 and CSS font-palette: Web Typography Gets Colorful]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365677</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/colrv1-and-css-font-palette-web-typography/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T14:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to Toshi Omagari, the author of Arcade Game Typography, the world’s first multi-colored digital font was created in 1982 for a never-released video game called Insector. Multi-colored fonts, sometimes called chromatic type, are still relatively rare on the …
COLRv1 and CSS font-palette: Web Typography Gets Colorful originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ollie Williams</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Even Small UX Changes Can Result In An Increase In Conversion (A Case Study)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/sunuva-case-study-ux-changes-result-increase-conversion/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/sunuva-case-study-ux-changes-result-increase-conversion/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we will be taking a closer look at a design case study and discuss possible reasons why its customers abandon their online shopping carts and what solutions are recommended in each particular case.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Denis Studennikov)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s Create a Tiny Programming Language]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365650</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/lets-create-a-tiny-programming-language/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T13:56:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[By now, you are probably familiar with one or more programming languages. But have you ever wondered how you could create your own programming language? And by that, I mean:
A programming language is any set of rules that convert 
…
Let’s Create a Tiny Programming Language originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Md Shuvo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magical SVG Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/magical-svg-techniques/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/magical-svg-techniques/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-10T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Smart SVG techniques, from generative SVG grids to SVG paths with masks, grainy SVG gradients, cut-out effects and fractional SVG stars. Let’s look at some magical SVG techniques that you can use right away.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Useful Tools for Creating AVIF Images]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365579</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/useful-tools-for-creating-avif-images/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T15:00:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AVIF (AV1 Image File Format) is a modern image file format specification for storing images that offer a much more significant file reduction when compared to other formats like JPG, JPEG, PNG, and WebP. Version 1.0.0 of the AVIF specification …
Useful Tools for Creating AVIF Images originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sunkanmi Fafowora</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Game Changer: Browser Back/Forward Cache]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/performance-game-changer-back-forward-cache/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/performance-game-changer-back-forward-cache/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the end of 2021, the Chrome team shipped some functionality that has the ability to make or break sites meeting the Core Web Vitals. So, let’s learn a little bit more about the Back/Forward Cache (aka bfcache), and what you can do to test if your website is compatible with it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Serve a Subdomain as a Subdirectory]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365614</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/how-to-serve-a-subdomain-as-a-subdirectory/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T14:19:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s say you have a website built on a platform that excels at design and it’s available at example.com. But that platform falls short at blogging. So you think to yourself, “What if I could use a different blogging …
How to Serve a Subdomain as a Subdirectory originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Siciliano</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Give Effective Feedback Remotely]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/give-effective-feedback-remotely/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/give-effective-feedback-remotely/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-06T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s explore how to give and receive better feedback when working remotely — feedback that is actionable, specific, kind, and that won’t set you on edge. We’ll start by explaining when feedback sessions don’t work and how to prevent it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joshua Mauldin)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Resilience, Flexibility And Immediacy: Working With Headless Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/resilience-flexibility-immediacy-headless-systems/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/resilience-flexibility-immediacy-headless-systems/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-05T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When deploying websites, there’s rarely a one-size-fits-all solution. Some websites benefit from server-rendered pages, some prefer statically generating content upfront. In this article, Stefan explains how a CMS such as [Storyblok](https://www.storyblok.com/) can help you make your site more resilient without losing the flexibility to deliver time-relevant content.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stefan Baumgartner)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Syntax Highlighting (and More!) With Prism on a Static Site]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365510</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/syntax-highlighting-prism-on-a-next-js-site/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T14:16:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[So, you’ve decided to build a blog with Next.js. Like any dev blogger, you’d like to have code snippets in your posts that are formatted nicely with syntax highlighting. Perhaps you also want to display line numbers in the …
Syntax Highlighting (and More!) With Prism on a Static Site originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing A Better Language Selector]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/designing-better-language-selector/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/designing-better-language-selector/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How difficult can it be to design a bulletproof language selector? It’s not as straightforward as one might think. We need to avoid redirects, decouple our language and country presets, allow for overrides, and use non-modal windows. Let’s dive in!]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adding Custom GitHub Badges to Your Repo]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364932</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/adding-custom-github-badges-to-your-repo/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T14:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you’ve spent time looking at open-source repos on GitHub, you’ve probably noticed that most of them use badges in their README files. Take the official React repository, for instance. There are GitHub badges all over the README file that communicate important dynamic info, like the latest released …
Adding Custom GitHub Badges to Your Repo originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Nick Sypteras</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[You Don’t Need A UI Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/you-dont-need-ui-framework/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/05/you-dont-need-ui-framework/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-03T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Developers often reach for UI frameworks like Bootstrap or Material UI, hoping that they’ll save a bunch of time and quickly build a professional-looking app. Unfortunately, things rarely work out this way. Let’s talk about it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Josh Comeau)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating Realistic Reflections With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365491</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-realistic-reflections-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-05-02T14:14:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In design, reflections are stylized mirror images of objects. Even though they are not as popular as shadows, they have their moments — just think about the first time you explored the different font formats in MS Word or PowerPoint: …
Creating Realistic Reflections With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Preethi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make A Wish (May 2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-may-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-30T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s welcome May with a new collection of wallpapers. Designed with love by artists and designers from across the globe, they come in versions with and without a calendar for May 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Creating the DigitalOcean Logo in 3D With CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365447</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/creating-the-digitalocean-logo-in-3d-with-css/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T14:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Howdy y’all! Unless you’ve been living under a rock (and maybe even then), you’ve undoubtedly heard the news that CSS-Tricks, was acquired by DigitalOcean. Congratulations to everyone! 🥳
As a little hurrah to commemorate the occasion, I wanted to …
Creating the DigitalOcean Logo in 3D With CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jhey Tompkins</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Partytown Eliminates Website Bloat From Third-Party Scripts]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/partytown-eliminates-website-bloat-third-party-apps/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/partytown-eliminates-website-bloat-third-party-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-29T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introducing Partytown, a lightweight open-source solution that reduces execution delays due to third-party JavaScript by offloading third-party scripts to web workers, which run in background threads.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Steve Sewell)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Setting Up CloudFront to Host Your Web App]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365413</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/setting-up-cloudfront-to-host-your-web-app/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T14:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In my last article, we went over how to set up a web app that serves chunks and bundles of CSS and JavaScript from CloudFront. We integrated it into Vite so that when the app runs in a browser, …
Setting Up CloudFront to Host Your Web App originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Adam Rackis</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTA Modal: How To Build A Web Component]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/cta-modal-build-web-component/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/cta-modal-build-web-component/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Nathan Smith explains how to create modal dialog windows with rich interaction that will only require authoring HTML in order to be used. They are based on Web Components that are currently supported by every major browser.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Nathan Smith)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cool Hover Effects That Use Background Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365383</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/cool-hover-effects-using-background-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T14:20:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A while ago, Geoff wrote an article about a cool hover effect. The effect relies on a combination of CSS pseudo-elements, transforms, and transitions. A lot of comments have shown that the same effect can be done using background …
Cool Hover Effects That Use Background Properties originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Temani Afif</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Boosting UX With Design KPIs]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boosting-ux-with-design-kpis/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/boosting-ux-with-design-kpis/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-27T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We should be able to measure how well a particular design solves a particular problem. Let’s explore design KPIs that capture user’s experience, how to measure them and how to keep both users and business stakeholders happy, over time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avoiding the Pitfalls of Nested Components in a Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365359</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/nested-components-in-a-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T14:30:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When creating a component-based, front-end infrastructure, one of the biggest pain points I’ve personally encountered is making components that are both reusable and responsive when there are nested components within components.
Take the following “call to action” (<CTA />…
Avoiding the Pitfalls of Nested Components in a Design System originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dan Christofi</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Preventing Bad UX Through Integrated Design Workflows]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/ux-integrated-design-workflows/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/ux-integrated-design-workflows/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-26T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When bad UX has lingered in a product for so long, it can feel like a mountain to overcome. In this article, Ceara Crawshaw shares her advice on how you can invoke joy and assure the quality in the work done on product teams.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ceara Crawshaw)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What If Our Sliders Actually Slid?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/what-if-sliders-actually-slid-html-element-input-range/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/what-if-sliders-actually-slid-html-element-input-range/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Jhey Tompkins explores one of GreenSocks’ newest plugins alongside React to create an impractical whimsical spin on a well-known native element: ``.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Testing The CLI The Way People Use It]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/testing-cli-way-people-use-it/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/testing-cli-way-people-use-it/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-22T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever wondered, why do people write CLI tools? When is a good time to think about yours? Today we’ll touch on these questions, along with some tips to remember when creating one. However, all of this serves as a prelude to the real topic: end-to-end testing of CLI tools.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Georgy Marchuk)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Designing Better Navigation With Navigation Queries]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-navigation-ux-queries/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/designing-better-navigation-ux-queries/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-21T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In UX, we can use navigation queries, evaluation journeys, A-Z index and tap-ahead autocomplete to help users get where they want to be, faster. Let’s find out how.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Productivity Tips And Tools For A More Efficient Workflow]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/productivity-tips-tools/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/productivity-tips-tools/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-20T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a good timesaver? In this post, we compiled useful productivity tips and tools that help you speed up routine tasks, enhance your development workflow, and stay organized.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jamstack Rendering Patterns: The Evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/jamstack-rendering-patterns-evolution/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/04/jamstack-rendering-patterns-evolution/"/>
        <updated>2022-04-19T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Ekene Eze shares his thoughts about the direction of the web in 2022, and what solutions we can expect to see come up in the ecosystem to significantly improve the Jamstack experience.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Ekene Eze)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>