<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-03-28T00:07:28.301Z</id>
    <title>osmos::feed</title>
    <updated>2022-03-28T00:07:28.301Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.14.4</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HTML Starter Template – A Basic HTML5 Boilerplate for index.html]]></title>
        <id>62310caec3e3d106805db8b3</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/html-starter-template-a-basic-html5-boilerplate-for-index-html/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T23:18:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HTML has different tags, some of which have semantic meanings. A basic boilerplate for an HTML file looks like this:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Dillion Megida</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is a UX Engineer? User Experience Engineer Role Explained]]></title>
        <id>602b31e00a2838549dcc6253</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/what-is-a-ux-engineer/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T21:47:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I am currently a User Experience or UX Engineer for D2iQ. And lots of people ask me what exactly is a UX Engineer.  This question comes from designers and developers alike. So, I figured it was time to write about it to create awareness and demystify the role. This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Natalie Pina</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Java Enum – Enumeration in Java Example]]></title>
        <id>623c71ec138a19064b0642c4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/java-enum-enumeration-in-java-example/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T21:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An enumeration (enum for short) in Java is a special data type which contains a set of predefined constants.  You'll usually use an enum when dealing with values that aren't required to change, like days of the week, seasons of the year, colors, and so on. In this article,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Color and Text Styles in Figma]]></title>
        <id>62351427cdcd57069ddfb5e4</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-color-and-text-styles-in-figma/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T21:24:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, we'll be learning how to create, edit, and use color and text styles in Figma. We'll also learn how to combine color and text styles and use them to create beautiful designs. Styles help you simplify your workflow, keep text and layers consistent, and save valuable time.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ijelekhai Faith Olohijere</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remix Routes Demystified]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/remix-routes-demystified/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-25T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past months, there have been lots of talks dedictaed to Remix. Routing is not only one of the things that sets it apart from other frameworks, but it also fuels great performance and improves the overall experience for developers. Let’s dig in to all  of the features that build up routing in this powerful framework.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a freeCodeCamp Student Started a Business and Teaches Kids to Code]]></title>
        <id>6236afa1cdcd57069ddfb9e6</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/freecodecamp-student-started-business-teaches-kids-about-computers/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T22:55:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Original Article: 脑瘫、面包店、志愿者——“编程让我变得更真实” [https://chinese.freecodecamp.org/news/cerebral-palsy-bakery-volunteer-programming-makes-me-real/] Original Author: Miya Liu [https://chinese.freecodecamp.org/news/author/miyaliu/] In 2019, the freeCodeCamp Chinese community launched the DevTalk interview program. We invited senior developers, Internet practitioners, and people with development backgrounds to share their experiences learning programming, working experiences, and other exciting stories.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Alan Luo</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to SSH into a Docker Container – Secure Shell vs Docker Attach]]></title>
        <id>6234b763cdcd57069ddfb192</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-ssh-into-a-docker-container-secure-shell-vs-docker-attach/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T19:47:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Containers are the bread and butter for running applications today. And the most popular container technology is called Docker [https://www.docker.com/].  Knowing how to SSH into a container is essential to using, debugging, and operating containers on your local operating system or remote setup.  This article will describe different]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sebastian Sigl</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Int Object is Not Iterable – Python Error [Solved]]]></title>
        <id>623c45ea138a19064b064195</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/int-object-is-not-iterable-python-error-solved/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:46:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you are running your Python code and you see the error “TypeError: 'int' object is not iterable”, it means you are trying to loop through an integer or other data type that loops cannot work on. In Python, iterable data are lists, tuples, sets, dictionaries, and so on. In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Kolade Chris</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Create Microservices with FastAPI]]></title>
        <id>623c9dd5138a19064b06449b</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/how-to-create-microservices-with-fastapi/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:43:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FastAPI is a Web framework for developing RESTful APIs in Python. It is a great choice when you want to build an app based on microservices. We just published a course on the freeCodeCamp.org YouTube channel that will teach you how to develop microservices app using FastAPI. In this course,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Beau Carnes</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[indexOf in Java – How to Find the Index of a String in Java]]></title>
        <id>62389b37cdcd57069ddfc5a0</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/indexof-in-java-how-to-find-the-index-of-a-string-in-java/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T16:11:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A string is a collection of characters nested in double quotes. The indexOf  method returns the index position of a specified character or substring in a string. In this article, we'll see the syntax for the different indexOf methods. We'll also look at some examples to help you understand]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Ihechikara Vincent Abba</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use UISearchController in iOS Apps]]></title>
        <id>62388dc7cdcd57069ddfc4d1</id>
        <link href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/news/learn-to-use-uisearchcontroller-in-ios-apps/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-24T15:55:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello everyone! In this article we are going to learn how to use UISearchController in iOS Apps. What are we going to build? We are going to build a movie search application which uses the TMDB [https://www.themoviedb.org/] API to fetch movie info and display it using a UICollectionView based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Sai Balaji K</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Those HTML Attributes You Never Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/html-attributes-you-never-use/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-23T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Louis Lazaris describes and demonstrates some interesting HTML attributes that you may or may not have heard of and perhaps find useful enough to personally use in one of your projects.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Louis Lazaris)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Good Design Is All About Good Timing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/design-is-all-about-good-timing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-22T12:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this shorter series of articles, we highlight design patterns, techniques, and strategies to design better digital interfaces. You can also learn much more in [“Smart Interface Design Patterns”](https://smart-interface-design-patterns.com/), a 6h-video course with 100s of hand-picked examples, curated by Vitaly.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way)]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363745</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/write-html-the-html-way-not-the-xhtml-way/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T20:08:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You may not use XHTML (anymore), but when you write HTML, you may be more influenced by XHTML than you think. You are very likely writing HTML, the XHTML way.
What is the XHTML way of writing HTML, and what …
Write HTML, the HTML Way (Not the XHTML Way) originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Jens Oliver Meiert</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows High Contrast Mode, Forced Colors Mode And CSS Custom Properties]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/windows-high-contrast-colors-mode-css-custom-properties/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-21T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Properties can be used for far more than just color, and their values update in realtime, both via display mode updates and JavaScript logic. This is powerful stuff. Eric explains how modern CSS is a powerful piece of assistive technology that can thread into it to create flexible, maintainable and adaptive digital experiences.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Eric Bailey)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364090</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/optimizing-svg-patterns/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T22:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I recently created a brick wall pattern as part of my #PetitePatterns series, a challenge where I create organic-looking patterns or textures in SVG within 560 bytes (or approximately the size of two tweets). To fit this constraint, I have …
Optimizing SVG Patterns to Their Smallest Size originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Bence Szabó</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Make A Drag-and-Drop File Uploader With Vue.js 3]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/drag-drop-file-uploader-vuejs-3/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-18T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Building on a previous article on How to Build a Drag-and-Drop File Uploader, we’ll be adding some new features, but more importantly (maybe), we’ll be learning how to build it in Vue 3 and learn some best practices for Vue along the way.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Joseph Zimmerman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Claymorphism: Will It Stick Around?]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/claymorphism-css-ui-design-trend/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[This fresh new design trend has been picking up steam with the rising popularity of colorful inflated 3D graphics in web illustrations and with the latest Virtual Reality projects like “Horizon Worlds”. Let’s see if there is room for Claymorphism on the UI, and how we can create this effect with CSS.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Adrian Bece)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean!]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=365042</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-tricks-is-joining-digitalocean/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-15T12:18:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey!
I’ve got a big announcement to make here. (Where’s my gong? I feel like this really needs a good gong hit.)
CSS-Tricks, this very website you’re looking at, has been acquired by DigitalOcean!
You can hear …
CSS-Tricks is joining DigitalOcean! originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Improving The CI/CD Flow For Your Application]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/improving-ci-cd-flow-application/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Looking for ways to create a smooth CI/CD flow for your software? In this article, Tom Hastjarjanto shares some useful concepts that can be combined with GitHub Actions and NPM packages. With this setup, you will be able to release multiple times per hour with a fully documented trace managed by Git.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Tom Hastjarjanto)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Complete Guide To Mobile App Marketing]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/guide-mobile-app-marketing/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-11T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Standing out among the millions of mobile apps can be challenging, but proper marketing can give you that crucial edge. This piece shares how to start your mobile app marketing strategy and improve it as you go while keeping up with the latest trends in the market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Sona Dabaghyan)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[An Introduction To AWS Cloud Development Kit (CDK)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/introduction-aws-cloud-development-kit/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-10T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this article, Vivek Maskara introduces Amazon Web Services’ (AWS) Cloud Development Kit (CDK) which is increasingly becoming a popular tool for managing AWS-based infrastructure. We’ll take a closer look into CDK concepts, and then how to use the AWS CDK toolkit to deploy a sample application to an AWS account.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vivek Maskara)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Audio Visualization With JavaScript And GSAP (Part 2)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part2/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-09T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What started as a case study turned into a guide to visualizing audio with JavaScript. Although the output demos are in React, Jhey Tompkins isn’t going to dwell on the React side of things too much. The underlying techniques work with or without React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Performance Signals For Customizing Website UX]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/signals-customizing-website-user-experience/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-07T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Using signals to deliver less, or different, content is a form of progressive enhancement (or graceful degradation depending on how you look at it), whereby extraneous content is only loaded when necessary, but the core functionality of the website still works. In this article, we’ll look at some of the signals that can be used for this.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Barry Pollard)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Create An Information Architecture That Is Easy To Use]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/easy-information-architecture/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/easy-information-architecture/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-04T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If users cannot find the answers to their questions or are not exposed to critical messaging, they will not act, and your website will fail. To prevent that from happening, you need an effective information architecture. In this article, Paul Boag provides you with a process to ensure you have precisely that.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Paul Boag)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say Hello to selectmenu, a Fully Style-able select Element]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363972</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/the-selectmenu-element/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T15:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I want to introduce you to a new, experimental form control called <selectmenu>. We’ll get deep into it, including how much easier it is to style than a traditional <select> element. But first, let’s fill in some context …
Say Hello to selectmenu, a Fully Style-able select Element originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Brosset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Build Membership Businesses with Memberful]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364001</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/build-membership-businesses-with-memberful/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T15:33:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[(This is a sponsored post.)
What would your business be like if you sold memberships? It might be more than fun to think about, in fact, it might just be transformative. With membership, would you include little add-ons or …
Build Membership Businesses with Memberful originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Web Layouts For Dual-Screen And Foldable Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/building-web-layouts-dual-screen-foldable-devices/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/building-web-layouts-dual-screen-foldable-devices/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-03T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dual-screen devices are just the next evolution in responsive design. If you have a PWA or website, the APIs available make integrating into your existing code base seamless. This article explains why it’s an exciting time for layout on the web, and how dual screens provide an opportunity to get even more creative.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Stephanie Stimac)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[7 Fresh Links on Performance For March 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364350</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/performance-links-february-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T21:26:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I have a handful of good links to articles about performance that are burning a hole in my bookmarks folder, and wanna drop them here to share.
The new WebPageTest website design
From fonts to SVG: an icon migration strategy
…
7 Fresh Links on Performance For March 2022 originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Make a “Raise the Curtains” Effect in CSS]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363882</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-raise-the-curtains-effect/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T15:57:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[“Raise the curtains” is what I call an effect where the background goes from dark to light on scroll, and the content on top also goes from light to dark while in a sticky position.
Here’s an example where I …
How to Make a “Raise the Curtains” Effect in CSS originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Silvestar Bistrović</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Guide To Audio Visualization With JavaScript And GSAP (Part 1)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part1/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/audio-visualization-javascript-gsap-part1/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-02T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What started as a case study turned into a guide to visualizing audio with JavaScript. Although the output demos are in React, Jhey Tompkins isn’t going to dwell on the React side of things too much. The underlying techniques work with or without React.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Jhey Tompkins)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CSS Custom Highlight API: The Future of Highlighting Text Ranges on the Web]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363724</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/css-custom-highlight-api-early-loo/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T17:41:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Styling ranges of text in software is a very useful thing to be able to do. Thankfully, we have the CSS Custom Highlight API to look forward to because it represents the future of styling text ranges on the web.…
CSS Custom Highlight API: The Future of Highlighting Text Ranges on the Web originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Patrick Brosset</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed: Use Cases For CSS fit-content]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364351</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ahmad-shadeed-use-cases-for-css-fit-content/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T15:41:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ahmad Shadeed covers the CSS fit-content sizing keyword. It’s useful! It just doesn’t come up super often. I find myself using min-content a lot more, like when setting up the height of a grid-template-row.
The fit-content keyword is actually …
Ahmad Shadeed: Use Cases For CSS fit-content originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New CSS Features In 2022]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/new-css-features-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/03/new-css-features-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-03-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2022 is shaping up to be a pretty great year for CSS, with a plethora of new features on the horizon. Some are already starting to land in browsers, others are likely to gain widespread browser support in 2022, while for one or two the process may be a little longer. In this article we’ll take a look at a few of them.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Michelle Barker)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=364346</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/ie-down-edge-up-global-browser-usage-stats-are-for-cocktail-parties-and-conference-slides/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T23:14:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[I enjoy articles like Hartley Charlton’s “Microsoft Edge Looks Set to Overtake Safari as World’s Second Most Popular Desktop Browser.” It’s juicy! We know these massive players in the browser market care very much about their market share, so when …
IE Down, Edge Up… Global Browser Usage Stats Are for Cocktail Parties and Conference Slides originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Chris Coyier</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[We All Are Ukraine 🇺🇦]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/we-all-are-ukraine/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T18:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a design community, we all can’t be silent in these times. We need to be united in our fight against the war, for democracy, for those dreams that children are entitled to have when they are growing up. It’s our obligation to help as much as we can. **We are donating all proceeds** from "Interface Design Checklists" PDF to support Ukraine.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Vitaly Friedman)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think]]></title>
        <id>https://css-tricks.com/?p=363929</id>
        <link href="https://css-tricks.com/web-component-pseudo-classes-and-pseudo-elements/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T15:37:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ve discussed a lot about the internals of using CSS in this ongoing series on web components, but there are a few special pseudo-elements and pseudo-classes that, like good friends, willingly smell your possibly halitotic breath before you go …
Web Component Pseudo-Classes and Pseudo-Elements are Easier Than You Think originally published on CSS-Tricks. You should get the newsletter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>John Rhea</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[March For Equality (2022 Desktop Wallpapers Edition)]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/desktop-wallpaper-calendars-march-2022/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Following our monthly tradition, artists and designers from across the globe challenged their creative skills and designed desktop wallpapers to welcome March. They come in versions with and without a calendar and can be downloaded for free.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Cosima Mielke)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Recipe For A Good Design System]]></title>
        <id>https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/</id>
        <link href="https://smashingmagazine.com/2022/02/recipe-good-design-system/"/>
        <updated>2022-02-28T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Maintaining a design system is a lot of work. In this article, Atila Fassina shares his lessons learned and how a platform such as Backlight can help put together a series of tools to speed up your architecture setup.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>hello@smashingmagazine.com (Átila Fassina)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>